Come on... Come on, kid!
يالا ، يالا به
Don't... fuck...
نه
We're gonna make it. Fuck!
ما موفق مي شيم ، لعنتي
Come on, Oleg. Stay with me!
يالا اولِ ، يش من بمون
Come on!
يالا
I'm not sure we're gonna make it.
ما موفق مي شيم
We're gonna crash!
داريم تصادف مي کنيم
We're good.
خوبه
It's all looking very good.
همه ي خوب به نظر مي ياد
Nobody fucking moves! Get down on the ground.
هي کي تکون نخوره همه بخوابيد رو زمين
- Get down. - Now, you cocksuckers!
بريد ايين  - کس کش ها -
You heard him! Get down!
مه نشنيديد ، بخوابيد رو زمين
You're making the biggest fucking mistake...
داريد اشتباه بزري مي کنيد
Shut up! Down, motherfuckers! Down!
خفه شو ، برو ايين ، مادر جنده
Everybody! Eat the fucking floor!
همه بخوابيد رو زمين
Now, very fucking carefully
همه تون حواستون رو جمع کنيد
Reach into your jackets and take out whatever you're packing
دست کنيد تو جيب تون و هر ي توش هست
and slide it under the bed. -Fuck you...
بندازيد زير تخت
Come on! All of you! Move it!
سريع تر ، همه
Come on, fuckheads! Keep it moving. Now!
همه تون ، کله کيري ها
You better spend it real quick, shit bags.
بهتره اين کار رو سريع انجام بدي
You ain't long for this fucking world
ديه توي اين دنيا ي کيري جايي براي تو نيست
Yeah, right, I’ll be sure to have a Mai Tai on you.
... آره ، الان يه فن" ماي - تاي" بهت مي زنم که
On all you goombah fucks.
تا کونت اره شه
Ja, man. I’ll have one on you too.
منم يه فن به تو ميزنم
- Go, go, go! Come on! - Move! Move! Move!
سريع تر ، سريع  - بجنبيد ، بجنبيد  -
Hurry up! Fucking move!
سريع تر ، بجنبيد
Let's go, let's go, let's go!
بزن بريم
Come on
سريع
Come on! Now!
سريع تر
Motherfucker!
مادر جنده
No, man.
تو رو خدا
We don't give a fuck about these niggers.
ما به اون کاکا سياه محل سم نمي زاريم
Piss on Perello blood. Fuck him!
زِر نزن ، بُکنش
I don't think so.
من اين جوري فکر نمي کنم
Son of a bitch!
حرومزاده
I don't give up you fuck!
مي يرم مي کنمت
What? Where you going, you fuck? We can work this out. Let's talk.
يه ؟ کدوم وري داريد مي ريد؟ مي تونيم با هم حرف بزنيم
Fuck you!
اييدمت
Shut...the fuck up!
خفه خون بير
Where the fuck you reaching? Huh?
به هدفتون رسيديد؟ هان؟
Please...
خواهش مي کنم
Tell you what, have a Mai Tai on me, huh?
مي خواستي به من فن "ماي - تاي "بزني؟
Fuck me. He's a cop!
اييده شديم ،اون يه ليسه
A fucking cop!
يه ليس کس کش
Motherfucker!
مادر جنده
Get the shit and let's go. Now!
کاسه کوزه رو جمع کنيد ، بايد بريم
Hurry the fuck up!
عجله کنيد
Fucking dirty mooks
ليس هاي لعنتي
Fucks
لعنتي
Is there one fucking honest cop in this fucking city?
يه ليس خوب تو اين شهر تخمي يدا نمي شه؟
Joey.
جويي
Give me your gun.
تفنت رو بده من
Take this shit and get rid of it, and do me a favor.
اينا رو بير و يه جوري م و ور کن تا خيالم راحت بشه
Don't fuck it up.
ند نزني
Move!
بدو
Never, dickwad!
نمي زارم ، لعنتي
Sorry. Are you OK?
معذرت مي خوام ، خوبي؟
Oh, shit. I didn't mean to do that.
اوه ، نمي خواستم اين جوري بشه
Hey, boss.
سلام رئيس
You whacking off to the E channel again? Huh?
رو ناه مي کني؟ هان؟Eداري دوباره کانال
Just wanna smell you. Just like that.
فقط مي خوام بوت کنم
You didn't call, you son of a bitch.
را تلفن نزدي ،کس کش
Let me guess. My pearls you've been promising?
مه تو قول نداده بودي؟
It’s nothing, just a little recycling.
يزي نيست ، فقط يه حال وحول ساده
Joey, come on.
جويي ، تو رو خدا
If Tommy ever found out about that...
اه تامي يزي در اين باره بفهمه
Sshh.
هيس
Just remember, it's just our little insurance policy, all right?
بدون که اين فقط يه راه بيمه کردنه
Cos there's no way in hell I’m gonna be thinking about getting some of this...
اين کار خراب نمي شه ون من در مورد جوانبش فکر کردم
looking at you through some glass window. There's no fucking way.
من داشتم تو رو از شت شيشه مي ديدم اره ي ديه اي ندارم
Now, Joey, come on. No, no, no, no
نه ، جويي ، نه
No. No!
نه ، نه
Come on, baby. Baby, look at me.
يالا عزيزم ، به من ناه کن
- What? - Nicky's around.
ي؟  - نيک همين دور و برِ؟
Nicky's busy. I’ll be quick and real quiet, come on.
نيک سرش شلوغه من اين کار رو سريع و بي سر وصدا انجام ميدم
Quiet? I don't think so. Quick, i can believe.
بي سر وصدا ، من که فکر نمي کنم
- You know something, Mrs. G? - What?
مي دوني يه خانوم جي؟ يه؟-
You're bad.
تو خيلي بدي
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
آره ، آره ، آره
- I’ve got a rep. - Yeah? You got a rep?
من يه جنده ام - آره ، تو يه جنده اي  -
You got a cruisey rep?
تو يه فاحشه اي
I heard she likes to make it on washing machines.
شنيدم که اين کار رو رو ماشين لباس شويي دوست داره انجام بده
On select occasions. What else?
يا يه جاي بهتر؟
Oh, no, no, no. My sauce!
اوه ، نه ، غذام
- My sauce is burning! - Wait, that's how i like it!
غذام سوخت  - وايسا ؛ من اين جوري دوست دارم -
Yeah.
آره
- Fuck! Come on! - Hey!
لعنتي بيا  - هي  -
You use language like that, you ain't getting no after-dinner dessert.
ون اون جوري حرف زدي بهت دِسر نمي دم
Go find Nicky. I think he's up in the bedroom with Oleg.
برو دنبال نيکي فکر کنم با اولِ تو اتاق باشه
Why's he always with that Russky kid? Don't he have no other friends?
را اون همش با سر روسي مي رده؟ دوست ديه اي نداره؟
Joey, you know, they get along. it's fine. What do you want?
جويي ، اونا خيلي وقته با هم دوست هستند تو ي مي خواي؟
I don't want him going over there no more. That's what I want.
من نمي خوام ديه با اون دوست باشه فقط همين
I know. He knows.
مي دونم ، اونم مي دونه
He knows.
اونم مي دونه
I’ll go get him.
مي رم بيارمش
Yo, Nick. Dinner.
نيک ، بيا شام
- Oh, shit.
اوه لعنتي
Come on.
بدو
Get down.
برو ايين
Dinner.
شام
Can Oleg stay?
اولِ مي تومه بمونه؟
It’s already been three times this week.
اين سومين بار تو هفته ست
I’m sure his mom would like to have him home.
من مطمئنم که مادرش مي خواد که اون بره خونه
It’s OK. I’m not even hungry.
باشه ف من الان رسنه ام نيست
I’ll see you tomorrow. Go Razors.
فردا مي بينمت
You, go wash up. Those hands are scary.
برو دستات رو بشور خيلي کثيف شدن
Good night, Oleg.
شب بخير اولِ
Good night, Mrs. Gazelle.
شب بخير ، خانوم َزِل
He's not even up there.
اون بالا نبود
They turned the basement into a sports complex again.
اونا  انبار رو به يه ورزشاه تبديل کردند
- How many times am I supposed to tell him? - What do you want? They're just boys.
ند دفعه اينو بهش فتم؟  - تو ه انتظاري داري؟ اونا به هستند -
Dad, I won't do it again, I swear.
بابا ، من قول مي دم ديه اين کار رو نکنم
Don't you expect me to make book on that.
انتظار نداري که ازت تشکر کنم؟
Now, go get your grandfather.
حالا برو در بزر رو بيار
I just washed my hands.
من دستام رو شستم
All right.
خيلي خوب
Hey, Nick.
هي نيک
Razors and Blues Friday night. 1 20 yellow, pal.
رِيزورز  و  بلوز ، جمعه شب ، تو يِلو ال
No way!
خداي من
It’s gonna be a death match between Chester and Erlich!
اين يه مسابقه ي مر و زندي بين ستر و الريکِ
They're going home in body bags!
اونا آش و لاش بر مي ردند خونه
Red ice!
Red ice!
Hey, can Oleg come?
اولِم مي تونه بياد؟
He's never been to one game, and he's...
اون تا حالا هي بازي رو از نزديک نديده
Not this time. Sal could only score me a pair of tickets.
نه  اين دفعه آخه "سال "فقط دو تا بليط به من داده
Maybe next time, though.
شايد دفعه ي بعد
Go get your grandfather.
برو در بزر رو بيار
Come on, man. Make it different this time.
يالا،مرد ، اين دفعه يه کار ديه اي بکن
Get up.
بلند شو
I said, get up!
فتم بلند شو
What is this?
اين ديه يه؟
Wolfgang Puck. It's your favorite.
اين غذاي مورد علاقه ات استWolfgang Puck
It’s thick crust, you damn blyad.
اين خيلي کلفت شده، لعنتي
I cut off crust for you. It will be better.
من وشت ها رو برات تکه تکه مي کنم که بهتر بشه
Bring me out a Moskova.
بيار  moskova برام يه
Hey. Hey.
هي ، هي
Come here.
بيا اينجا
Come
بيا
Watch this.
اينو ناه کن
John Wayne in The Cowboys.
جان وِين تو نقش کابوي
I don't like cowboys.
من از کابوي ها خوشم نمياد
Come on.
بيا
It’s the Duke.
خيلي باحاله
Come, sit.
بيا بشين
When I was growing up in Kishinev
... وقتي من  تو "کيشينِف" بزر شدم
we had no VHS, no DVD back then.
ليرDVD اونجا نه ويدئو بود نه
I remember...
يادم مياد
I did a job for this friend of my father.
من براي دوست درم کار مي کردم
The man gave me as a reward this children's projector.
اون مرد به من يه جايزه داد
it came with three films.
سه تا فيلم به من داد
Speedy Gonzales, Tarzan Of The Apes, John Wayne in The Cowboys.
اسيدي ونزالز، تارزان و ميمون ها, و جان وين  در فيلم کابوي ها
I watched that thing a thousand times.
من اين فيلم ها رو هزار دفعه ناه کردم
Anzor, it's getting cold.
آنزور ، داره سرد ميشه
I was nine years old.
9سالم بود
I didn't know how long movies were supposed to be.
اون موقع نمي دونستم که زمان يه فيلم قدر بايد باشه
My version of The Cowboys, it was only 10 minutes long.
اون فيلم کابوي هايي که من داشتم فقط 10 دقيقه بود
No John Wayne getting shot.
که اصلا "جان وين "توش بازي نمي کرد
Because it was for kids, they left that part out.
براي اينکه براي ديدن به ها سانسور شده بود
I didn't know this...until I arrive in America
من اين رو نمي دونستم تا وقتي که اومدم آمريکا
and see it on TV for the first time.
و اون فيلم رو تو تلويزيون ديدم
I hate it. I want my 8mm back.
ازش بدم اومد، من همون قديمي رو مي خواستم
Because on that one, the Duke lives.
ون تو اون قديميه "دوک" هنوز زنده بود
Some things were better in the old place.
بعضي يزا قديميشون بهتره
Not too many. Some things.
نه همه يزا،فقط بعضي ها
Let me show you from the beginning.
بذار تا از اول بهت نشون بدم
No, no, no. Not forward.
نه ،نه جلو نه
This part's better.
اين قسمتش بهتره
Without the Duke?
بدون دوک؟
Where are you going?
کجا داري مي ري؟
You don't walk out on the Duke!
تو نمي توني دوک رو بيخيال بشي
Govnyak!
ُونياک
She said he's always distracted and he never finishes his work,
اون مي فت که اون  ديوونه ميشه و هي موقع کارش رو تموم نمي کنه
and she wants to get him tested.
مي خواد اون ببره آزمايش بده
She wants to get him tested? Tested for what?
مي خواد اون ببره آزمايش بده؟ آزمايش ي؟
I think maybe err...attention disorder or something.
فکر کنم در مورد اختلال حواس
I’m not fucking ADD.
من اون اختلال حواس کيري رو ندارم
Hey! You don't use that word in front of your mother.
هي ، ديه اون کلمه رو جلوي مادرت نو
- What's wrong with ADD? - The other one, smartass.
اختلال حواس ديه يه؟  - منظورم يکي ديه ست ،لاشي  -
He don't use that word, period.
اون اين کلمه رو تکرار نمي کنه
I don't wanna be on medication. You can't make me take it.
من نمي خوان تحت معالجه قرار بيرم نمي تونيد منو مجبور کنيد
Don't even worry about it. There's no way in hell anybody's gonna put you on meds, OK?
نران نباش ، اين که مي خوان تو رو معالجه کنن زيادم سخت نيست
Tell that teacher to come to the rink and watch him wax that puck.
به معلمش بو بياد هاکي بازي کردن و روي اون به رو کم کردنش رو ببينه
- That's perfect concentration every time. - That's different, Joe.
اون هميشه تمرکز خوبي داره  - اين فرق داره جو  -
We're just trying to find out what's going on with you.
ما فقط مي خواييم بدونيم تو ته؟
She said some great things too.
البته معلمتون يزاي خوبي هم فت
She said that he's very bright, that he's very creative.
اون فت اون خيلي باهوشه و همنين فعال
You left that part out before. I like that part.
اينو قبلاً هم فته بودي
I got potential.
من با استعدادم
You taking a collection down there?
تو اون ايين رو به ند کشيدي
He must eat.
اون بايد غذا بخوره
The little prick insults the Duke...
اون به دوک توهين کرد
..he don't eat in this house.
.اون تو اين خونه غذا نمي خوره.
You hear me, you little snot face?
صدام رو ميشنوي؟ با اون صورت تخميت
Stay in your room!
تو اتاقت بمون
Faggot!
مي کشمت
He's a growing boy.
اون يه سر به ست
What did I fucking say, Sukka?
مه من ي فتم ، سوکا؟
He has to eat, Anzor.
اون بايد غذا بخوره ، آنزور
Please.
خواهش مي کنم
Who puts food on this fucking table?
کي غذا رو ميزاره رو اون ميز کيري؟
Not you, blyad.
تو نيستي
I’m the big man of this house.
من مرد اين خونم
When I say the little shit don't eat, he don't eat.
وقتي ميم اون نبايد غذا بخوره اون غذا نمي خوره
Anzor.
آنزور
John Wayne was a faggot.
جان وين يز بدرد نخوريه
So Vicki Gilleto told me she saw you walking hand in hand with Jeannie's daughter.
ويکي يلِتو بهم فت که با دختر جيني دست تو دست داشتي قدم مي زدي
- The fat one?
اون دختر اقه؟
Sounded like a gun.
انار صداي تفن اومد
Hey, Nick, throw me some bread.
هي ، نيک ، يه کم نون بده من
Oh, shit, get down! Get down!
اوه ، لعنتي بريد ايين ، بخوابيد
Are you OK? You OK?
حالتون خوبه؟ حالتون خوبه؟
Jesus, Joe. What the hell?
خداي من ، جو ، ه اتفاقي افتاده؟
Stay here. Motherfucker.
همين جا بمونين ، مادر جنده
- Motherfucker! I’ll kill that fucking piece of shit. - Where are you going?
مادر جنده، من اون وهِ لعنتي رو مي کشم - داري کجا مي ري؟  -
You Russian piece of shit!
تو وهِ روسي
Fucking cunt.
کس کش
Shoot my fucking house. I’m gonna fucking kill you.
به خونه يمن شليک مي کني مي يرم مي کنمت
Dad, wait!
بابا ، وايسا
Get back in the house. Get back in the house!
بررد خونه
Get back in now! Go!
بررد تو
Don't you move.
تکون نخور
You piece of shit.
وه ِ لعنتي
- I’m gonna fucking kill you! -Nick, get inside.
من تو رو مي کشم - نيک ، برو تو -
Joe. Joe! What's the matter with you?
جو ، جو ، ت شده؟
I just called 911. Leave it for the cops!
من زن زدم 911 بذار ليس حلش کنه
There's a kid in here! Get back in the...
يه به اون توئه شما بريد تو
I’m gonna kill you! Open the fucking door!
من تو رو مي کشم اون در کيري رو باز کن
- Oleg's my friend! - Get inside.
اول دوست منه  - برو تو -
- Open the door. - Joey, don't be a damn hero!
در رو باز کن  - جويي ، نمي خواد قهرمان بازي درآري -
Open up! It’s Joey Gazelle from next door! Open up!
در رو باز کن ، من جويي ازل ، همسايتون هستم
Open up.
در رو باز کن
Get back. You get back.
عقب وايسا
Where is he? Is he upstairs?
اون کجاس؟ اون طبقه ي بالاست؟
- His room. - What?
تو اتاقش - ي؟ -
- Get down.
دراز بکش -
What the fuck?
ه اتفاقي افتاده؟
Where's the kid? Huh?
به کجاست؟ ها؟
- Where's the kid? - Fuck him. I’m the one who's shot.
به کجاست؟  - لعنت به اون ، من اونيم که تير خورده -
Who is it? Is he still in the house?
اون کيه ، هنوز تو خونه ست؟
The little snot fuck ran out back.
اون به ي ر رو فرار کرد
Oleg?
اول؟
Oleg? What are you trying to say? Oleg shot you?
اول؟ ي مي خواي بي؟ اول به تو شليک کرد؟
What are you?
او کي هستي؟
A fucking idiot?
يه آدم خرفت؟
I didn't do this to myself.
من خودم اين کارو با خودم نکردم
The little prick would've done me too.
اون خراش کويکم من درست کردم؟
Look at him.
اونو ناه کن
Jesus, it's a fucking miracle.
خداي من ، اين يه معجزه ست
Where'd he get the fucking piece?
اون تفن رو از کجا آورده؟
- Fuck should I know? - What, it wasn't yours?
من از کجا بدونم؟  - ي ، اون تفن مال تو نبود؟ -
No! No way!
نه ، اصلاً
I got a .357 in the safe out back.
من يه دونه 357 تو کمد دارم
He had some fucking snub-nose thing.
اون يه دونه کلت داشت
Silver. Chrome.
نقره اي ، کُروم
Bullshit! Now you tell me. I’m not playing around.
لعنتي ، همين الان بهم بو من شوخي نمي کنم
We saw where you put the gun but he didn't take anything.
ما با هم ديديم که تو اونا رو قايم کردي ولي اون يزي بر نداشت
- Not with me. - Well, he went back, Nicky.
نه وقتي با من بود - خوب ، اون برشته نيکي -
I didn't know. I swear I didn't know.
من نمي دونم ، قسم مي خورم که نمي دونم
Come here. Listen to me. Listen to me.
بيا اينجا ، به من وش بده ، به من وش بده
That piece? That's not just any hot piece.
اون تفن؟ اون يه تفن عادي نيست
- Tommy used it to burn a dirty cop. - Oh, no. Joe...
تامي از اون براي کشتن يه ليس استفاده کرده - اوه ، نه ، جو -
Yeah. Listen. On top of it, that kid's out there right now.
آره ، وش کن علاوه بر اين هنوز اون به اونجاست
The cops are on their way. If they find the gun, or they find the kid and he talks, I’m dead.
ليس ها تو راهند، اه اونا تفن رو يدا کنن يا با اون به حرف بزنن، من کلکم کنده ست
- Fuck! - Calm down. Calm down.
لعنتي - آروم باش ، آروم باش -
Calm down. We can get to him.
آروم باش ، ما يداش مي کنيم
- You can get to the gun before the cops do. - Oh, shit.
تو مي توني اونو قبل از رسيدن ليس ها يداش کني - اوه ، لعنتي -
Hey.
هي
- Where are you gonna take him? - Memorial.
کجا د ارين مي برينش؟  -
Hey, Mila, you should go with him.
هي ، ميلا ، تو بايد باهاش بري
I’m gonna look for Oleg. Me and Nicky are gonna go find him, OK?
من دارم دنبال اول مي ردم من و نيکي يداش مي کنيم ، باشه؟
I’ll get Teresa to stay here in case he comes back.
من به ترسا مي م اينجا بمونه تا موقعي که اون بررده
- You should go. - Thanks, Joey.
تو بايد بري - مرسي ، جويي -
- Yeah, no problem. - I’m sorry.
باشه ، مشکلي نيست - معذرت مي خوام -
We're gonna find him. Don't worry about it.
ما يداش مي کنيم، نران نباش
Motherfuck.
مادر جنده
Come on.
يالا
Police officers. Sir, do you live here?
افسر ليس، آقا شما اينجا زندي مي کنيد؟
No. No, actually I live next door.
نه ، نه من تو خونه  کناري زندي مي کنم
I heard gunshots, so I came to see what's going on.
من صداي تفن شنيدم خوب اومدم ببينم ه اتفاقي افتاده
- What did you see? - Err...
شما ي ديد؟ - ... ار  -
I saw Anzor, my neighbor, in the kitchen. He'd been shot.
من آنزور ، همسايمون رو تو آشزخونه ديدم  - به اون شليک کرده بودند
- See who did it? -No, he was screaming in Russian.
کي اين کار  کرده؟ - نه، اون داشت به روسي داد و فرياد مي کرد -
His wife asked me to stick around for the kid.
همسرش از من خواست که دنبال سرش بردم
- You don't know who shot him? -No.
شما نمي دونيد کي به اون تير زد؟ - نه -
I’m gonna need to take a statement outside.
مي خوام اون بيرون ند تا سوال ازتون برسم
I can't have you messing up the scene.
من نمي تونم بذارم شما صحنه جرم رو خراب کنيد
Hey, check it out.
هي ، يه بازرسي بکن
I don't see nothing inside. Maybe all the way back.
من هي ي اون تو نديدم
Forget it. Leave it for Forensics.
فراموشش کن ، بسر به فرانسيس
Sir, I need for you to wait outside.
جناب ، ازتون مي خوام بيرون وايستيد
All right. No problem.
باشه ، مشکلي نيست
I’m fucking having a heart attack.
داشتم سکته مي کردم
- Breathe. - I gotta find this kid. I gotta find this kid tonight.
نفس بکش - من بايد اين به رو امشب يدا کنم -
Nick, I need to know places. I need to know hideouts.
نيک ، من بايد از مخفياهتون با خبر بشم
Go to your room and make a list. Nick, make a list!
بروتو اتاقت و يه ليست تهيه کن
- OK. - I’m not fucking around, Nick.
باشه - من جايي نمي رم ، نيک -
Joe, just take it easy.
جو ، فقط آروم باش
There's no fucking time!
من وقت ندارم
I want you to wait next door.
ازت مي خوام جلوي در همسايه وايسي
The second he shows up, call me.
هر موقع که اون خودش رو نشون داد به من زن بزن
I can't have to keep fucking talking to the cops.
من نمي تونم با اون ليس ها حرف بزنم
You understand me? The fucking gun is on the street.
مي فهمي من ي ميم؟ - اون تفن الان وسط خيابونه -
This whole fucking things about to blow up.
آب شده رفته زير زمين
If Tommy or any of those fucking guys find out about it I’m a dead man
اه تامي يا يدونه از رفيقاش يداشون بشه من کلکم کنده ست
You gotta fucking help me
تو بايد به من کمک کني
Yeah, if I fucking have to.
من مجبورم
Grab your jacket. We're going for a ride.
ژاکتت رو بوش ، بايد بريم دنبالش
All right, Nick. I want you to stay in the car, all right?
خيلي خوب ، نيک مي خوام که تو ماشين بموني ، باشه؟
Don't get out for anything.
به هي وجه از ماشين نميري بيرون
If I’m not back in one hour, call your mother. She'll come and get you, OK?
اه من تا يه ساعت ديه بر نشتم به مادرت زن بزن ، اون مياد تور رو ميبره
Excuse me.
ببخشيد
Who's in the other room? Is that Yugorsky, gunshot victim?
کي تو اون اتاقه؟ آقاي يوورسکي اون توِ؟ بهش شليک شده
Teenager. DUI car wreck. I think they just lost a GSW in 3.
يه به ست ، تصادف کرده فکر کنم داره مي ميره
Lost?
ميميره؟
- He's dead? - Yeah.
اون مرده؟  - آره -
No, wait, he took a bullet right here.
نه ، اون اينجاش تير خورده
No, major trauma to chest. He's been in surgery all day.
نه اون زخمش شديد بود تمام روز تو اتاق عمل بود
The guy was a cop.
اون يه ليس بود
Oh, wait. Yeah, they did bring someone in about 40 minutes ago.
اوه ، آره 40 دقيقه يش يه نفر رو آوردن اينجا
OR number 2. He's gone upstairs already.
تو اتاق شماره 2 اون طبقه بالاست
That's this way?
از اين طرف؟
Can I help you, Dr Donaldson?
مي تونم بهتون کمک کنم ، دکتر دونالدسون؟
Yeah, the cops are waiting outside.
آره ، ليس ها اون بيرون منتظرند
They need to run a match on this bullet asap.
اونا مي خوان رو اين فشن تحقيق کنند
I’ll make sure they get it right away.
من مطمئنم که همين الان روش تحقيق کردند
Excuse me.
ببخشيد
You looking for this? Yugorsky? GSW shoulder?
شما دنبال اين مي شتيد؟ يوورسکي؟ جراحت شانه؟
You gotta help me find him, Nick.
تو بايد به من کمک کني تا يداش کنيم ، نيک
- What are you gonna do to him? - I’m not gonna do nothing.
مي خواي با اون ي کار کني؟  - کاري نمي خوام بکنم -
I just need to get my gun back and bring him home.
من فقط مي خوام تفنم رو بيرم و اونو برردونم خونه
You sure?
تو مطمئني؟
Talk to me, Nick.
حرف بزن ،نيک
There's this old abandoned rec centre in the park
توي ارک يه جا ي مخفي هست
Me and Oleg would hang out there sometimes read comics
من و اول بعضي وقت ها اونجا کتاب مي خونيم
He might he there
اون شايد اونجا باشه
Nice gun.
ه تفن قشني
Detective Rydell, Narcotics.
کارااه رايدل ، روانشناس
I already made a statement.
من قبلاً هم فتم
don't know who the shooter was
من نمي دونم کي به من شليک کرد
Fucking niggers all look the same.
فکر کنم يه کاکا سياه بود
Yeah. Anzor Yugorsky.
خوب ، آنزور يوورسکي
Any relation to Ivan Yugorsky?
با ايوان يوورسکي نسبتي داري؟
My uncle.
عمومه
The Czar of Brighton Beach. I’ve been to his club a couple of times.
تو ساحل برايتون من ند وقتي به کلوش مي رفتم
Nice joint.
آدم خوبي بود
He even sang a few songs.
اون حتي ند تا آهنم بلد بود بخونه
He sings like a fucking toad.
اون مثل يه وزغ کيري آواز مي خونه
Well, Sinatra he's not, but he's a man with a serious reputation.
خوب ، اون سيناترا نيست ولي آدم معروفيه
- He has a lot of enemies. - Bullshit.
اون دشمناي زيادي داره - لعنتي -
I told you it was just some fucking crack head.
من فقط فتم اون ند تا دوست کله خر داشت
Yeah. Well, I spoke to the officers on the scene.
خوب ، من با افسر ها در محل جنايت حرف زدم
There was no sign of forced entry.
هي نشونه اي  دال بر اينکه کسي زوري اومده باشه تو نبود
But they did find some interesting shit out back.
حتي اونا لوله رو هم  يدا نکردند
- Come on. Where? - It’s this way.
بيا ، کجاست؟
Let's go. Come on.
بدو ، يالا
Come on.
يالا
Go, go, go.
برو ، برو
This way.
از اين طرف
Be cool. And let me do all the talking.
آروم باش ، من فقط حرف ميزنم
I’m gonna get you out of here.
مي خوان تو رو از اينجا ببرم بيرون
- Help you? - Yeah.
مي تونم کمکت کنم؟  - آره  -
How much you got?
قدر مي توني کمک کني؟
Oh, I got a lot.
اوه ، خيلي زياد
Yes.
آره
Oleg, it's Nicky. Are you in there?
اول ، من نيکيم ، تو اونجايي؟
- This the spot? - Mm.
همين جاست؟  - آره -
Hey, where's the stash?
مخفياهت کجاست؟
Last stall, motherfucker.
يداش کن ، مادر جنده
Find the stash. Find it.
مخفي اه رو يدا کن يداش کن
Go on. Find it.
بدو ، يداش کن
We're gonna search this entire park. He might still be around.
ما بايد همه ارک رو برديم اون شايد هنوز تو ارک باشه
What the fuck do you think you're doing, white boy?
فکر م کني داري ي کار مي ني به سفيد  وست؟
All right, drop it, or I’ll fucking waste the midget. Come on!
بندازش ، ور نه اين به رو مي کشم يالا
Plug 'em, Dell. Fuck it, man! Fuck 'em up.
بکشش مرد ، بکشش
All right, stay right by me.
خيلي خوب ، کنار من بمون
Right here. Against the wall.
همين جا جلوي ديوار
Don't you move. Stay right there.
تکون نخور ، همون جا بمون
I didn't do nothing, Officer. I just came to...
سرکار من کاري نکردم ... من فقط اومدم تو
Put your fucking head against the fucking stall.
اون کله کيريت رو بذار زمين
Put your fucking head there!
سرت رو بذار اونجا
Oleg.
اول
I told you to stay outside.
بهت فتم بيرون وايسا
- Did you find him? - Get the fuck outside! Get out of here!
يداش کردي؟  - بيرون وايسا ، برو بيرون  -
I’m talking to you! What did you see?
دارم باهات حرف مي زنم ، تو ي ديدي؟
Find a gun? You find a silver gun? Did you find a fucking silver gun?
تو يه تفن يدا کردي؟ يه تفن نقره اي؟ تو يه تفن نقره اي کيري يدا کردي؟
I-I-I got no gun.
من ، من تفني يدا نکردم
You wanna study for the GED? Here
اينجا مطالعه کني؟ هان؟GEDتو مي خواي در مورد
Look what you done to my fucking ride, bitch.
ببين با ماشين من ي کار کردي؟ جنده تي؟
Jesus, please, baby. Please.
خداي من ، خواهش مي کنم عزيزم
I’ve only been taking one class. One class two hours a week.
من فقط مي خوام تو يه کلاس شرکت کنم يه کلاس ، 2 ساعت در هفته
I still got time to be pulling tricks.
من هنوز وقت دارم
And what do I get in return?
و من ي رو بايد برردونم؟
- Fucking night school? - I’ll quit!
مدسه شبانه؟  - ديه نمي خوام -
I’m super proud of you for showing some initiative.
من بخاطر ابتکارات به تو افتخار مي کنم
Maybe I’ll even come to your graduation.
حتي شايد به مراسم فارغ التحصيليت هم بيام
But first you're gonna give me back my fucking property.
ولي اول وسايلم رو بهم بر مي ردوني
You learn how to use that watching Sesame Street?
بلدي ه جوري از اون استفاده کني؟
You ain't even holding it right.
تو حتي اونو درست نه نداشتي
What's the matter, kid? You got the shakes?
ي شده به؟ را داري مي لرزي؟
Whoops.
بکش کنار
Now I’m gonna put a smile on your face, boy.
حالا مي خواي يه نقاشي رو صورتت بکشم؟
Cheek to cheek.
از اين لُ تا اون لُ
You're gonna be the happiest little brat in school.
تو خوشحال ترين به کيري تو مدرسه اي
Say cheese.
"بو "سيب
Who's laughing now, you fucking grey meat limp-dick motherfucker?
حالا کي ميخنده؟ مادر جنده
Mac Daddy!
M ac Daddy !
Puñeta!
Pueta!
You got some cojones, kid.
برو ي کارت ، به
Let me see your fingers, son.
سرم ، بذار انشتات رو ناه کنم
Is this... Hey! Is this your son?
اين سر شماست؟
I’m taking care of him tonight, OK?
من امشب ازش مراقبت مي کنم؟ باشه؟
Unless you have the number of his doctor and I can get a prescription over the phone,
يا شماره دکترش رو مييرد تا من باهاش حرف بزنم
you'll have to take him to Emergency.
يا اينکه مي بريدش اورژانس
- If you want me to call you a cab... - I don't need no fucking cab!
ارم بخواييد زن مي زنم ليس  - من به اون ليس هاي لعنتي احتياجي ندارم -
I need some spray shit for him!
من فقط يه اسري لعنتي براي اون مي خوام
That spray shit is a controlled substance, ma'am, so what can I tell you?
اون اسري لعنتي مواد کنترل شده داره خانوم من ي مي تونم به شما بم؟
- Keep the change. - I can't... This is stupid. I can't do this.
بقيه اش مال خودت  - نه ؛ من نمي تونم اين کار رو بکنم  -
Listen, why don't we go in the back and talk about it, OK?
را نمي ريم اون شت تا راجع بش حرف بزنيم؟
- Look, lady... - I’ll take care of you.
خانوم ناه کنيد  - من ازت خوشم اومده -
- There's nothing I can do, lady. - There's nothing you can do?
من کاري نمي تونم بکنم ، خانوم  - تو کاري نمي توني بکني؟ -
- Take him to Emergency. - OK.
ببرش به اورژانس  - باشه  -
OK.
باشه
Nothing you can fucking do?
او کاري نمي توني بکني؟
Get what he needs. Now.
هر ي اون احتياج داره بده ، همين الان
- It’s Beclovent. - Yeah, I know.
Becloventاون - آره ، فهميدم  -
Beclovent, bitch!
جنده Beclovent
Come on, let's just go back.
يالا ، بيا بررديم
No.
نه
If he turns up, your mom's gonna call.
اه اون برشته بود ، مادرت زن مي زد
Tee.
تي
Sal.
سال
Yeah.
باشه
- Do girls really get naked in there? - You'll find out when you're 21.
واقعا زن ها اينجا لخت ميشن؟  - وقتي 21 سالت شد مي فهمي  -
I’ve seen Mom naked. It's no big deal.
من مامان رو ديدم وقتي لخت شده بود اتفاقي نيوفتاد
Trust me on this one. It's always a big deal.
به من اعتماد کن در اين مورد ،اين يه اتفاق بزره
Stay here.
همين جا بمون
What?
ي ؟
It’s taken care of.
اون منتظرتونه
Oh. It's taken care of. Lucky us.
اوه، اون منتظر ماست
Guys sit down Have a seat
به ها بشينيد
Don't be shy.
خجالت نکشيد
They make a good Mai Tai for a twat bar, but seriously overpriced.
اونا "ماي تاي" رو خوب اجرا کردند ولي قيمتش خيلي بالاست
Two million dollars for a round of drinks.
دو ميليون دلار براي يه دور مشروب
And the pussy ain't even that hot.
و جنده هاي اينجا هم خيلي باحال نيستند
Jody, I’m doin' business here. Jody! Come on, get the fuck out of here.
جودي ، من اينجا کار د ارم جودي ، ورت رو م کن
Two million dollars.
دو ميليون دلار
Suck a dick, you prick bastard. You don't have shit on us.
لعنتي ، مه اينجا سرِ ردنه ست تو مي خواي مارو نابود کني
What do you think of this?
نظرت راجع به اين يه؟
Cops never found these at the scene. Just two dead narcs and three dead Jamaicans.
ليس ها اينا رو هرز تو صحنه جنايت يدا نکردند فقط دو تا جاسوس و 3 تا جاماييکايي مردند
Ballistics is gonna reveal the slugs that killed my partners
لوله شناسي معلوم کرد که لوله اي باعث مر والدينم شده که
didn't come from the Jamaicans.
از جاماييکا نيومده
So there were others involved.
اما کساي ديه اي هم در ير ماجرا هستند
As for myself...erm...I was never there.
درست مثل من كه هي ربطي به اين ماجرا نداشتم
Well...
... خوب
dead guys tell no tales.
آدم مرده يزي واسه فتن نداره
Yeah. Why don't you ask your pal here?
آره ، را از شريكت نمي رسي؟
What the fuck you talking about?
داري راجع به ي حرف مي زني؟
You blew my partner Stevie's balls off with a .38 snub nose.
تو همكار منو با يه كلت شماره 38 زدي
A real distinctive piece.
با يه دونه تفن تابلو
Stainless. Polished up like a spic's hubcap.
ضد زن و تر تميز
Now, let me take a wild guess here.
بذار يه حدسي بزنم
I think you gave him the gun to dump in the river
فكر كنم كه شما تفناتون رو به اون د اديد كه بندازدش تو رودخونه
Now I’m assuming that he never got around to it because two hours ago
من الان وانمود مي كنم كه اون 2 ساعت يش اين دور و بر نمي لكيد‍‍
his next-door neighbor took a slug in the shoulder
وهمنين همسايه اش بهش شليك شده
The shooter was the guy's 10-year-old stepson.
و تير انداز سر خونده ي 10 ساله اش بوده
Who was over at Gazelle's house two hours earlier.
كي 2 ساعت يش تو خونه زل بوده
What the fuck you trying to do here? Huh?
ي مي خواي بي؟
You trying to fucking play us?
تو مي خواي با ما بازي كني؟
You're wasting your time, and this is bullshit.
تو داري وقتت رو تلف مي كني و اين خيلي بده
Bullshit? Bullshit, huh?
بده؟ هان ؟ بده؟
This punk, Anzor Yugorsky?
اون بدبخت ،آنزور يوورسكي؟
He describes the gun to me in vivid detail.
اون همه يز رو به من با جزئيات توضيح داد
- The fuck is this guy talking about? - He's talking about a fucking shiny gun.
اين رت و رت ها كه اين ميه در ه مورده؟ - اون داره راجع به يه تفن براق حرف ميزنه  -
Big deal. There's a thousand on the street. it ain't the piece.
مثل همون هزارتايي كه تو خيابوناست و هي ربطي هم  به ما نداره
Oh, yeah? What were you doing at the hospital when they brought Yugorsky in? Huh?
اوه آره؟ س تو بيمارستاني كه اين يارو يوورسكي رو آوردن ي كار مي كردي؟
Sniffing around Emergency
داشتي تو اورژانس قدم مي زدي
You know what I figure?
ميدوني منظور من يه؟
I figure you were there to pull a switch on the slug they took out of him
من تو رو ديدم كه داشتي دنبال لوله مي شتي
My wife asked me to go to the hospital.
همسرم از من خواست كه برم بيمارستان
She was concerned, in a neighborly way. She wanted me...
اون نران همسايمون شده ... از من خواست كه
All right, you know what? Enough bullshit. I expect to find a bag...
خيلي خوب ، مي دوني يه؟ ... من انتظار دارم كه يه كيف
in this locker at Down Neck Station by midnight.
تو صندوق امانات ايستاه نك درست تو نيمه شب يدا كنم
If the bag is not there one minute after,
ار يه دقيقه اون ور تر كيف اونجا نباشه
I’m taking you all down any fucking way I can.
من از هر طريقي كه بتونم درتون رو در مي آرم
Even If Ihave to manufacture the case
حتي اه بتونم مدارك رو جعل مي كنم
And you know I will. Cos I got the toughest mob in the world.
و شما مي دونيد كه مي كنم ونكه من خفن ترين آدمي هستم كه تا به حال ديد
I’m the law.
من قانونم
Right, stay put. I’m gonna grab you a burger.
خيلي خوب، تو ماشين بمون تا برات يه همبرر بخرم
- I’m not hungry. - You didn't finish dinner, I’ll grab you something.
من رسنه ام نيست  - تو شامت رو كامل نخوردي ، يه يزي برات مي خرم 0
Stay here.
همين جا بمون
Dad?
بابا؟
Don't go in there. Let's just go home.
اونجا نرو ، بيا بريم خونه
It’s gonna be all right.
همه ي درست ميشه
No, it's not.
نه ، نميشه
- Hey, Frankie. How you doing? - Hey. How are ya?
سلام ، فرانكي ، اوضاع طوره؟  - سلام ، حالتون خوبه؟  -
- It’s good to see you. - Sit, Joe.
خوشحالم كه  مي بينمت  - بشين جويي  -
- How you doin,' guys? - Hi, Joey.
ي كار مي كنيد رفقا؟ - سلام جويي -
How you doing?
اوضاع طوره؟
- You want some coffee, or something to eat? - Nah, I’m good.
يزي واسه خوردن مي خواي؟  - نه ، مرسي -
But I got my boy waiting out in the car.
ولي من به سرم فتم اون بيرون منتظر باشه
- I wanna get him a burger. - Tony, take care of that.
مي خوام براش يه همبرر بيرم  - توني ، ترتيبش رو بده -
Yeah, Tony, get him some fries and a strawberry shake.
آره ، يك كم سس توت فرنيم روش بريز
Don't scare him. He don't know you're coming.
نترسونيش ، اون نمي دونه كه شما اينجاييد
So Joe
خوب جو
I got off the phone with Ivan about this thing with his nephew.
من شت تلفن همه يز رو به ايوان توضيح دادم
I told you, it's not the fucking piece.
من بهتون فتم كه اين اون تفنه نيست
Look, everybody knows the nephew is a brain -fried reprobate.
من مي دونم كه اين يارو خيلي بي شرفه
Yeah, whatever. He's a tweaker piece of shit.
آره ، اون خيلي بي شرفه
And he's cooking meth in his backyard.
آره ، اون تو حياطش وشت ميزه
It’s just a matter of time before he blows up the neighborhood.
اون حتي راجع به روابط با همسايه اش يزي نمي دونه
We know this. But it's a sensitive issue with me, Joe.
ما اينو مي دونيم ولي اين براي من خيلي حساسه ، جو
I’m in bed with Yugorsky on this gasoline deal.
من اين يارو يوورسكي رو از اون معامله ي بنزين مي شناسم
Hey.
هي
It’s a good deal.
اين يه معامله خوبه
- I don't wanna rock the boat. - Oh, fuck that.
من نمي خوام همه يز خراب بشه - لعنتي  -
Fuck those Russian cunts. Huh?
اون كس كش هاي روسي رو اييدم
Pop, it's the fucking narc that's got his dick in our ass.
ا، اونا كيرشون رو كردن تو كون ما
Hey.
هي
Calm down Tommy
آروم باش تامي
that maybe you were looking to knock him out of the cooking business
شايد تو بخواي كه اون يارو ديه تو حياطش وشت نزه
and helped the boy out.
و به اون سر كمك كن تا اين كار رو انجام بده
Made a piece available to him.
همه يز رو براي اون آماده كن
I would never use a kid to do something like that.
من يه به رو مجبور نمي كنم كه اين كار رو بكنه
Never.
هرز
All right, all right, look.
باشه ، باشه ، ناه كن
I need a person to make assurance to the russky
من مي خوام تا يه نفر اين كار رو بكنه
that I'll have my entire crew in the street out looking for that kid.
خوب ، من به همه نيروهام تو خيابونه احتياج دارم تا اون سره رو يدا كنم
Now, in the interest of professional harmony...
خيلي حرفه اي و رو نظم
..I think we all wanna get our story straight.
فكر كنم هممون مي خواييم كه همه يز درست بشه
You agree don't you Joe?
تو موافقي جو؟ نه؟
One hamburger and you're out of my life. That's it.
يه همبرر برات مي خرم و تو از زنديم ميري بيرون
Oleg.
اول
Oh shit!
لعنتي
Hey, kid.
سلام به
How you doing? Your old man sent this stuff out for you.
طوري؟ بابات اينو برات فرستاده
Thanks.
ممنون
Ain't it a little late for you to be out? I have twins your age. They're in bed by now.
يه كم دير نشده  كه بيرون باشي؟ من دو تا دوقلو هم سن تو دارم كه الان تو تخت خوابن
What are you, like, nine?
ند سالته؟9؟
Ten.
ده سال و
And a half.
نيم
I gotta go to the bathroom.
بايد برم دستشويي
Hey, Joey.
هي ، جويي
Looks like your kid don't listen too well.
مثل اينكه به ات زياد حرف وش كن نيست
Hey, Nicky. Get over here.
هي ، نيك ، برو بيرون
Get over here
از اينجا برو بيرون
What you doing? I told you to wait in the car.
ي كار  داري   مي كني؟ مه بهت نفتم تو ماشين بمون؟
- I had to go to the bathroom. - How you doing, Nicky?
بايد برم دست شويي  - حالت طوره نيكي؟
Want some Gummy Bears?
يه كم بادوم مي خواي؟
Hey, Nicky.
هي ، نيكي
You wouldn't by chance...
... تو به طور اتفاقي نمي دوني
know where your friend got that gun?
كه رفيقت تفن رو كجا ذاشته؟
Would ya?
مي دوني؟
No.
نه
I have to go to the bathroom.
بايد برم دست شويي
- OK -Nick, you go to the bathroom.
باشه - نيك برو دست شويي -
Have you decided yet?
هنوز تصميم نرفتي؟
I have a bus to catch and... Oh, no!
... من يه رئيس دارم كه
I’ll have a cheeseburger and a Coke.
من يه يز برر مي خوام با يه نوشابه
I gotta go to the bathroom.
بايد برم دست شويي
Don't worry, we're gonna take care of the cop.
نران نباش ، ما مواظب ليس ها هستيم
- I know. - OK.
مي دونم  - باشه -
Where is it?
كجاست؟
Hey, Nick.
هي ، نيك؟
- Where the hell are you? - Almost done.
كدوم وري هستي؟ - الان تموم ميشه  -
Razors with razors.
ريزور ها با ريزورها
Come on, wash your hands. We gotta get out of here. Come on.
يالا ، دستات رو بشور بايد از اين جا بريم
Fuck!
لعنتي
Hey, sweetie. How you doing?
سلام عزيزم ، حالت طوره؟
All right, Nick, listen to me.
خيلي خوب ، نيك ، خوب به من وش بده
I want you to think about where your friend might be,
مي خوام خوب فكر كني ببيني دوستت كجاست
because the others are looking for him and if they find him...
ونكه بقيه هم دنبال اونن ... و ار اونو بيرند
- They won't find the gun. - What did you say?
اونا تفن رو يدا نمي كنن  - ي فتي؟  -
What did you say?
ي فتي؟
Don't mess with me. I want you to fucking talk to me now.
منو اذيت نكن الان به من توضيح بده
- Promise me you won't hurt him. - I don't have time for this shit.
قول مي دي كه بهش صدمه نزني؟ - من براي اين وقت ندارم -
- Now fucking tell me. - Promise.
همين الان حرف بزن  - قول بده  -
Promise you what? What? I promise. I swear to God!
ه قولي بدم؟ باشه به خدا قسم
I’m not gonna hurt your friend! Come on. Tell me.
من به دوستت صدمه نمي زنم يالا ، بو ديه
Just tell me what you know.
فقط بو ي شده؟
Come on.
يالا
This one here?
اين يكي؟
Where is it? I thought you said you put it in there.
كجاست؟ مه نفتي ذاشتيش اينجا؟
- I did. I put it right... - Then where is it?
را ، خودم ذاشتم  - س كجاست؟  -
- I thought you said you put it in the tank. - I put it in here!
مه نفتي ذاشتيش اون تو؟ من ذاشتمش اون تو  -
Oh, shit.
لعنتي
Which one did you put it in, Nick? Huh?
تو كدوم يكي ذاشتيش؟
Goddamn it, Nicky.
لعنتي ، نيكي
Why did you lie to me? Why did you lie to me?
را به من دروغ فتي ؟ را؟
I didn't.
دروغ نفتم
- Why did you lie to me? - I’m not...
را به من دروغ فتي؟  - نفتم  -
- I’m not fucking lying! I put it in there!
من دروغ نفتم ،ذاشتمش اون تو-
You just fucking killed me, Nick.
تو منو به كشتن مي دي ، نيك
You just fucking killed me!
تو منو به كشتن مي دي
I want you to keep an eye open.
مي خوام كه شمات رو خوب باز كني
If you see anybody coming, I want you to cough really loud, all right?
اه كسي اومد تو ، با صداي بلند سرفه كن
- You're like a broken record. - I’m telling you, you gotta see this thing.
تو مثل يه نوار شكسته مي موني - من بهت فتم كه اونو مي بيني -
You better not be jerking my chain.
بهتره با من شوخي نكني
- What are you doin' here, kid? - I was looking for the bathroom.
اينجا ي كار  مي كني؟ دنبال دست شويي مي شتم  -
- Even the kid thinks it's a shithole back here. - Shut up, Ralphie.
حتي به هام فكر مي كنن اينجا ر از وهه - خفه شو ، رالفي -
All right, listen.
خيلي خوب ، وش كن
You go on out through that door,
از اون در برو بيرون
turn left, go all the way down to the end,
برو سمت  ، راهرو رو تا ته برو
turn left again, and you're there.
و دوباره برو سمت
You got it?
فهميدي؟
- Come on. - Err...which door?
يالا - كدوم در؟  -
Come here, kid. Come here.
بيا اينجا ، به ، بيا
Hey, Yolanda. Wait up!
هي ، يولاندا ، صبر كن
- Where you going with my cheesecake? - It’s for paying customers Not you
با اون كيك نيري من كجا داري  ميري؟ - اون براي مشتريي كه ول مي ده ،نه تو
I’ve got your number, fucker.
شمارت رو يدا كردم ، لعنتي
Forget it. I ain't dragging your butt across no state lines.
از جون من ي مي خواي؟
Look, bubba, why don't you just go home?
ناه كن ، را نمي ري خونت؟
I bet you things are not as bad as you think they are.
من بهت قول مي دم كه يزا اينقدر كه تو فكر مي كني بد نيست
Come on, bubba.
بيا ، عزيزم
Oh, mother...
اوه ، مادر جنده
- Hands where we can see 'em!
دستات رو ببر بالا
Over here.
اونجاست
Run! Run, little man! Run!
بدو بدو ، مرد كوك
Hey.
هي
Get off! Get off!
ولم كن ، ولم كن
Do you know these guys?
تو اينارو مي شناسي؟
- Yeah. - Babe?
آره - عزيزم؟  -
- Where the hell are you? - I’m taking care of things
ي كار داري مي كني؟  - مراقب اوضاع هستم -
Forget about it - they picked up Oleg at a bus station with a hooker.
فراموشش كن ، ون  اونو  با يه جيب بر رفتن
Who picked him up?
كي اونو رفته؟
- The cops? - Yeah.
ليس ها؟  - آره -
Jesus Christ, this is fucking bullshit.
خداي من ، ه بد شد
- Hey. - Fuck!
هي - لعنتي -
Hey! You got Nicky with you?
نيكي با توِ؟
Yeah, he's right here.
آره ، اون الان اينجاست
Then stop using your mouth around him!
جلوي اون اينجوري فحش نده
And bring my son home! Now!
و سرم رو بيار خونه، الان
Yeah. That's what I’m doing. I’m bringing him home right now.
باشه ، الان دارم ميارمش خونه
Ah. Do you mind?
مي فهمي؟
I’m feeling kind of parched.
من حس بدي دارم
Big game Friday night.
جمعه يه بازي قشن هست
I bet you're excited about that, huh?
من خيلي هيجان دارم
It’s gonna be red ice, and plenty of blue shirt body bags.
red iceتيم و هزاران طرفدارش
Am I right?
درست مي م؟
Look...I could help you, kid.
ناه كن ، بذار كمكت كنم
You and your mom, if need be.
البته اه تو و مادرت به اين كمك احتياج داشته باشين
Now I could get that prick out of your life.
من مي تونم زندي شما رو نابود كنم
Lock him up. I could do that, I’m a cop.
من مي تونم اونو تو زندان نه دارم مي تونم ، ون يه ليسم
All you have to do is tell me where you found the gun.
فقط به من بو اون تفن ُ از كجا آوردي؟
And where you stashed it.
و اونو كجا قايم كردي
That's it.
همين
What do you say?
ي  ميي؟
You'll let me help you.
بذار تا كمكت كنم
Get out of here, Mila.
از اين جا برو ، ميلا
You know? Go to a shelter.
برو دنباله يه سر ناه
I can get you an address.
من مي تونم بهت يه جا معرفي كنم
You don't understand.
تو نمي فهمي
I belong to him.
من به اون تعلق دارم
No. No.
نه ، نه
No, no, I don't understand.
نه ، نه، من نمي فهمم
I was prostitute in Moscow.
من تو مسكو خود فروشي مي كردم
Yugorsky Escort Service offered to bring girls over with promise of big bucks.
دار و دسته يوورسكي دخترها رو عرضه مي كردند
We would owe 50 thousand dollars. You know, pay back through work.
ما 50 هزار دلار بهشون بدهكار بوديم بايد با كار كردن ول  رو بهشون بر مي ردونديم
I take offer.
من شروع به كار كردم
Not tell them I’m pregnant.
ولي بهشون نفتم كه حامله ام
When they find out...
وقتي اونا فهميدند
..they insist I have an abortion.
منو مجبور كردن كه سقطش كنم
I tell them no.
ولي من فتم نه
They send Anzor to kill me.
اونا آنزور ُ فرستادن تا منو بكشه
Anzor's not a killer.
آنزور يه قاتل نبود
He's not...a hard man like big Yugorsky.
اون مثل يوورسكي بزر ، وحشي نبود
He thinks...
... اون فكر مي كنه
..he thinks he's John Wayne.
اون فكر مي كنه كه جان وينه
Wants to do right thing.
اون دوست داره كار هاي خوب انجام بده
He goes against his uncle, and tells big man Yugorsky he will pay off my debt.
اون جلوي عموش ايستاد و به يوورسكيه بزر فت كه اون بدهيش رو ميده
His uncle refuses...
عموش امتناع كرد
..and tells him...
و بهش فت
he will send others to kill me.
كه ند نفر ديه رو مي فرسته تا منو بكشه
So Anzor make me wife.
آنزور با من ازدواج كرد
Big man Yugorsky can't kill his nephew's wife.
يوورسكي بزر نمي تونست زن برادزاده اش رو بكشه
But he...tells Anzor to leave Little Odessa.
ولي به آنزور فت اُدِسا رو ترك كنه
He's no longer working for Yugorsky family.
اون ديه واسه خانواده ي يوورسكي كار نكرد
I’m gonna get you the name of a shelter.
من مي خوام آدرس يه سر ناه رو بهت بدم
You OK?
حالت خوبه؟
This ain't right, Joe. He don't need to be put through this.
اين درست نيست جو اون نبايد قاطي اين ماجرا بشه
Hey, Nick, I’m proud of you. You done good, all right?
نيك ، من به تو افتخار مي كنم كارت خوب بود ، نه؟
I’m gonna head up to Community Hills.
من رفتم اونجا
Cops don't got the gun yet but I may have a line on it so I’m gonna go over there.
ليس ها تفن رو يدا نكردند ولي من يه سرنخ يدا كردم كه مي خوام برم دنبالش
I’m scared, Joe.
من مي ترسم ، جو
I am pissed at you, and I am scared!
شاشيدم بهت من دارم مي ترسم
Be careful.
مراقب باش
- Hey.
هي   - هي  -
Just got word. The cops picked up the kid.
ليس ها اون به رو يدا كردند
- Anything you still wanna tell us? - Tell you what? There's nothing to tell.
هنوز يزي براي فتن نداري؟  - ي بم ، يزي براي فتن ندارم؟  -
- Where you headed, Joe? - Erm....
كجا داري مي ري، جو؟  - ... اممم  -
I was supposed to head to the store and pick up some milk and eggs.
فكر كنم داشتم مي رفتم مغازه تا يه كم شير و تخم مرغ بخرم
in all the excitement I forgot to do it, so...
علايقي كه فراموششون كردم
Yugorsky's gonna call us when he talks to the kid.
يوورسكي وقتي با اون به حرف زد به ما تلفن زد
Don't go too far
زياد دور نشو
- Later, Joe. - Yeah, see ya.
بعداً ميبينمت ، جو  - مي بينمت  -
Hey, Tee. Looking fucking good.
هي ،تي ، خيلي خوشل شدي
He keeps giving me this bullshit story about finding the gun
اونا اين ماجرا رو دادن به من تا موقعي كه اون تفن رو يدا كنم
The little fucker shot me. He ain't gonna spill dick to me.
اون به به من شليك كرد ولي نمي خواست كه اين كارو بكنه
You know, I don't think I’m being clear enough here.
فكر كنم زياد واضح حرف نزدم
You know what I mean?
مي دوني منظورم يه؟
Let me be crystal clear.
مي خوام صريح بم
You get the boy to give up Gazelle or I’m closing shop on your tweaker ass
تو اون سر رو مجبور مي كنه بيخياله َزِل بشه يا اينكه كونت رو اره مي كنم
and I’m taking you down fucking hard.
و تو را بياره مي كنم
Understand me?
فهميدي؟
Hey, cowboy.
سلام ، اورون
Wanna go get some ice cream?
يه كم بستني مي خواي؟
Get the fuck away from my car.
از ماشينم برو كنار
- Hey. Hey, I’m looking for Manny Perez. - He's not here.
هي هي ، من دنبال ماني رز مي ردم  - اون اينجا نيست  -
No! Oh, my God! I’ve never seen him.
اوه ، خداي من ، من اونو هرز نديدم
- Manny? Where the fuck is he? - He's not here!
ماني؟ اون كجاست؟  - اون اينجا نيست  -
- Where is he? Where is he?
اون كجاست؟ كجاست؟  -
Better not fucking lie to me!
بهتره به من دروغ ني
- Argh! - Where the fuck is he?
اون كجاست؟
- Where is he? - OK, OK!
اون كجاست؟  - باشه ، باشه  -
- He play cards at Armando's.
اون رفته كلو آرماندو تا ورق بازي كنه  -
- Armando's? - Uh-huh.
آرماندو؟  - آره  -
He's at Armando's. Yeah.
اون تو آرماندو؟
Get the hell out of the way! Just stay right there.
همونجا وايسا
- What's your name?
اسمت يه؟
- Conchita.
كونيكا  -
Now you listen to me, Conchita. You listen to me real good.
خوب به من وش كن كونيكا خوب وش كن
- I don't wanna hurt Manny. - OK.
من نمي خوام به ماني صدمه بزنم  - باشه  -
I don't wanna hurt him, but he has something that belongs to me.
من نمي خوام بهش صدمه بزنم اون يه يزي دستشه كه مال منه
- A gun. Do you know anything about a gun? -No, no.
يه تفن ،يزي راجع به تفن شنيدي؟  - نه ،نه  -
It’s block 5, number 602. That's where he is.
اون تو خيابون نجمه لاك  602
OK. Now listen to me.
باشه ، به من وش كن
We are now on what we call the honor system. You comprende?
ما الان دارين جوري با هم حرف مي زنيم كه بهش مي ن صداقت فهميدي؟
- You understand? - Si, señor.
آره  ، آقا  _
OK. You don't call Manny.
باشه ، تو به ماني زن نمي زني
You don't tell Manny I’m coming.
تو به ماني نمي ي كه من اومدم اينجا
You don't warn him for anything, cos if you do, I’m gonna come back here!
تو اونو از يزي با خبر نمي كني ون اه اين كارو بكني من دوباره بر مي ردم اينجا
I can be an asshole.
من مي تونم خيلي در سوخته باشم
You made your point.
تصميم خودت رو بير
You showed some balls.
تو يه يزايي مي دوني
I like that
كه من دوستشون دارم
But now it's time to be smart.
ولي الان وقتشه كه كله تو بكار بندازي
You tell me...what I want to know.
تو اون يزايي كه من مي خوان رو بهم مي ي
And I’m gonna reward you.
و من به تو جايزه مي دم
Razors season tickets
بليط هاي ريزور
- I’m sorry. - It’s OK.
متاسفم - مشكلي نيست -
I told you, we're cool.
بهت فتم آروم باش
- Just tell me. - I’m sorry I missed.
فقط بهم بو  - متاسفم ، من مش كردم  -
You little shit.
لعنتي
Tell me where the fucking gun is.
بهم بو اون تفن لعنتي كجاست
You tell me or I will fucking kill you!
بهم مي ي يا اينكه مي كشمت
Oleg!
اول
Where are you, you little shit?
كجا رفتي كثافت؟
I’ll find you!
يدات مي كنم
I’m gonna kill you!
مي كشمت
You're only making it worse on yourself!
تو فقط داري اوضاع رو براي خودت بدتر مي كني
You hear me?
صدام رو مي شنوي؟
Edele, I think we've picked up a stray.
ادل، فكر كنم اون م شده رو يدا كرديم
indeed.
راستي
Well, hello there.
سلااااام
- Hi - And who might you he?
سلام كي مي تونه اونجا باشه؟
- I think we should get another ice cream cone. - I think you're right, papa bear.
فكر كنم بايد يه بستني ديه بخريم  - فكر كنم راست مي ي  -
Hey. Hey.
هي ، هي
- You Manny? - Manny, no.
تو ماني هستي؟ - ماني ، نه  -
He's upstairs. What you want with him?
اون بالاست ، باهاش ي كار داري؟
Business.
كار دارم
If he owes you any money, forget about it.
اه بهت بدهكاره ، بهتره فراموشش كني
Ha! I just cleaned the cabron out.
من الان جيبش رو خالي كردم
Yeah? Who is it?
بله ، كيه؟
Heads down on the fucking table!
سرتون رو بذارين رو ميز
Heads down and hands behind your head! You move and I will fuck you up!
اه تكون بخوريد مي كشمتون
I will fuck you up! Don't you move!
مي كنمتون ، تكون نخوريد
Don't you fucking move! Get the fuck down!
تكون نخوريد ، بريد ايين
Which one of you is fucking Manny? Who's Manny?
كدومتون مانيه؟ ماني كيه؟
Manny's not here
ماني اينجا نيست
- Motherfucking pendejo! - Are you Manny?
مادر جنده تو ماني هستي؟
You know what the fuck I want! You called me pendejo, you fuck!
تو مي دوني من ي مي خوام به من فتي مادر جنده؟
I want my fucking gun! I want my fucking snub nose
من تفنم رو مي خوام
that you lifted from the fucking Arlington.
هموني كه از تو مغازه آرلينتون برداشتي
Now, where the fuck is it? Where the fuck is it?
خوب ، الان كجاست؟ كجاست؟
Fuck you! Where the fuck is my gun?
اييدمت ، تفنم كجاست؟
Your tool left a while ago
تفنت رو دادم رفت
Fuck! Fuck!
كثافت ، كثافت
Motherfucker!
مادر جنده
- Look at those braces - There's a little dimple there
موهاش رو ناه كنيد ه خنده اي
Yeah
آره
Yeah, that's super cute.
آره ، خيلي باحاله
isn’t this cool, huh? Yeah, come on. Look back in the camera.
باحال نيست؟ يالا، تو دوربين ناه كن
Try it again. Now you push that. Look in there.
يه بار ديه ، اون دكمه رو فشار بده
Oh, my gosh, yeah! You can see, right?
اوه ، مي توني ببيني؟
- It’s very smart. - Hey, Eric. You wanna hug your sister?
خيليب باحاله نه؟  - نمي خواي خواهرت رو بغل كني؟  -
- Yeah. Come on, please. - Just a little bit.
آره ، يالا  - يه كم بيشتر  -
- Get a little closer. - Come on. You guys love each other.
نزديكتر  - شما دو تا همدير دوست داريد  -
- You need a hug.
شما بغل كردن رو دوست داريد -
- A little closer - Come on.
نزديك تر  - يالا -
- Extend the arm
دستات رو باز كن
Come on, Come on Eric
يالا ، يالا اريك
You can do it a little better than that I mean that's your sister right?
تو اين كار رو بهتر مي توني انجام بدي منظورم اينه كه اون خواهرته،نه؟  -
Very good -You love your sister don't you?
خيلي خوبه - تو خواهرت رو دوست داري ، نه؟ -
What about you, Oleg? You wanna be in the film as well, don't you?
تو طور ، اول؟  - تو نمي خواي كه تو فيلم باشي؟  -
My stomach hurts. Can I go to the bathroom?
من دلم درد مي كنه ، مي خوام برم دست شويي
Sure.
حتماً
- I’ll just hold onto this. - Mm-hm.
من اينو برات نه مي دارم  -
Go outside.
مي ري بيرون
You take a right and then a left.
مي ري سمت راست ، بعد سمت
- Hurry up, though. You're missing out. - Mm.
عجله كن ور نه فيلم برداري رو از دست مي دي
- Who wants to play dress up? - Oh, good, dress up!
كي مي خوا لباساش رو عوض كنه؟  - اوه ، لباس عوض كردن  -
We have...the Burning Falcon.
داريمBurning Falconما اينجا .
And the Volt.
Volt  و
There you are. I thought you needed to go to the bathroom.
اينجايي من فكر كردم مي خواي بري دست شويي
I couldn't find it.
نتونستم يداش كنم
Silly boy.
سره احمق
I told you to take a right.
بهت فتم مي ري سمت راست
Then a left.
بعد  سمت
Come. I’ll show you.
بيا ، بهت نشون مي دم
Don't forget to wash your hands when you're done.
يادت نره وقتي كارت تموم شد دستت رو بشوري
Joe?
جو؟
- Mrs. Gazelle? - Who is this?
خانوم زل؟  - تو كي هستي؟ -
- Is this? - Oleg.
من اولم
I’m sorry about taking the gun.
من متاسف كه تفن رو برداشتم
- Oleg, where are you? - I think I’m in trouble
اول ، تو كجا هستي؟  - فكر كنم تو دردسر افتادم  -
Sweetheart I know what happened OK?
عزيزم، من مي دونم ه اتفاقي افتاده ، باشه؟
I need you to be straight up with me. Are the police listening in on this call?
مت ازت مي خوام كه با من صادق باشي ليس داره صداي مارو مي شنوه؟
No I’m not with the police
نه ، من با ليس ها نيستم
I’m at Dez and Edele's apartment.
من تو آارتمان دز و ادلم
I thi...I think they're gonna hurt us. - What?
فكر كنم اونا مي خوان مارو اذيت كنن  - ي؟  -
Oh Jesus
خداي من
Come on, come on. Is this some kind of a joke?
يالا ، داري شوخي مي كني؟
Oleg, you have caused enough trouble today.
اول تو امروز همه رو تو دردسر انداختي
- Where are you? - I don't know
الان كجايي؟  - نمي دونم ؟  -
I was in the hack of a van
منو با يه ون دزديدن
They brought us here. This room with all these toys.
مار و آوردن اينجا يه اتاق ر از اسباب بازي
They're making a video.
اونا دارن از ما فيلم مييرن
OK. OK, Oleg. I need you to look around for an address for me, OK?
باشه ، ازت مي خوام خوب بردي تا يه آدرس يدا كني باشه؟
Um...is there any mail laying around?
اونجا صندوق ستي يزي نمي بيني؟
I’m in the bathroom. She's gonna come back any minute.
من تو دست شوييم اون ند دقيقه ديه مياد
Bathroom, Jesus.
دست شويي ، خداي من
I don't know. I don't know.
نمي دونم ، نمي دونم
I don't know, um...
نمي دونم
Err I don't know Just, just call 911
نمي دونم ،زن بزن 911
No. I don't want to go back to the police.
نه ، من نمي خوام دوباره برم يش ليس ها
Why?
را؟
They want me to say I got the gun from Mr. Gazelle.
اونا منو مجبور مي كنن كه بم تفن دست منه
Do you need some help in there? - I’m OK
كمك مي خواي ؟  - نه ، مرسي  -
It’s my stomach I’m almost done
دلم درد مي كنه ، الان تموم ميشه
Oh, you poor thing.
اوه ، بياره
Well, I’m right outside.
خوب ، من بيرون منتظرم
- Oleg? - I’m still here
اول؟ من هنوز اينجام  -
OK.
باشه
OK. So look in the medicine cabinet.
تو جعبه كمك هاي اوليه رو ناه كن
Do you see any...any bottles?
يزي مي بيني ؟ بطري يزي؟
Prescription bottles usually have the address on the front label.
نسخه ها معمولا روشون آدرس نوشته  ميشه
Do you see anything?
يزي ميبيني؟
Just Is there anything in there?
يزي اونجاست؟
Oleg! What's happening?
اول ، اتفاقي افتاده؟
Oleg? It’s Dez. You wanna open up, please?
اول ، من دز هستم لطفاًدر رو باز كن
Oleg?
اول؟
Come on
يالا
Oleg! Oleg! Oleg?
اول
What's going on?
ه اتفاقي افتاده؟
- Just open the door! - Mrs. Gazelle, I got a bottle.
در رو باز كن  - خانوم زل ،من يه بطري يدا كردم -
So now read me the address.
خوب ، حالا آدرس رو برام بخون
- 1456, Owens Park Lane, Hoboken. Oleg open the door!
هوبوكن ،ارك اوون ، شماره 1456 اول در رو باز كن
Oleg!
اول
Let's go! Open the door!
يالا ، در رو باز كن
Oleg?
اول؟
Come on!
يالا
Oleg!
اول
Wake up. Wake up!
بلند شو، بلند شو
- We've gotta go get Oleg. Put your coat on. - I thought he was in jail.
ما بايد بريم اول رو نجات بديم ، لباست رو بوش من فكر كردم اون تو زندانه -
Hey, Holmes.
هي ، هلمز
- I got a busted headlight. - Hey, Lester, my man!
دادم كه راغ ماشين رو درست كني - هي ، لستر ، دوست من  -
Ouch. Who got over on you, bro?
كي تو رو زده؟
Some puta whose forwarding address is gonna be in ten different zip codes.
يه جنده
I got you covered by tomorrow night.
من ماشين رو فردا شب بهت مي دم
Hey, check this out.
هي ،اينو ناه كن
Is that sweet or what? Hey! A royal flush put her in my pocket.
هي ، يه دست خوب اونو ذاشت تو جيب من
- Three hundred cold puts her in mine. -No, man. She's a beauty.
300تا بهت مي دم كه مال من بشه نه، رفيق اون خيلي قشنه  -
Think I’m gonna hold on to her.
فكر كنم بايد برم سش بدم
Five hundred.
500تا
Al won't miss them. Not until Cinco de Mayo.
دلم براش تن ميشه
Oh, Joe! Shit!
اوه جو، لعنتي
I’m under a lot of stress tonight, so whatever I say don't count.
من امشب خيلي تو اضطراب بودم فحش هايي كه مي دم حساب نيستند
Do I still have to go to school tomorrow?
من هنوزم فردا بايد برم مدرسه؟
I don't know. We'll see.
نمي دونم ، بايد ببينيم طور ميشه؟
- Remember me? - Who the fuck are you?
منو يادت مياد؟  - تو ديه كي هستي؟  -
You got something that belongs to me. Snub nose .38.
تو يه يزي داري كه مال منه يه كلت 38
You scored it off of Manny in a card game. I need it back.
كه تو اونو از ماني تو بازي بردي حالا برش ردون
Fuck!
لعنتي
I want my fucking gun!
من تفنم رو مي خوام
Who the fuck are you huh?
تو كي هستي؟
Don't be fucking stupid!
احمق نباش
Fuck!
لعنتي
You fuck! You fuck! Where's my fucking gun?
مي كنمت ، مي كنمت ، تفنم كجاست؟
Help me! I’m burning!
كمكم كن ،دارم مي سوزم
Where's my gun? You gonna tell me where my gun is now?
تفنم كجاست؟ نمي خواي به من بي تفنم كجاست؟
If you don't tell me where I can find it you'll have third-degree burns. Know what that means?
اه بهم ني اون تفن كجاست مي ذارم تا به اندازه سوختي درجه 3 بسوزي ،مي فهمي يعني ي؟
No cock, asshole! You'll have a fucking melted dick!
اقو نه تو الان يه كير در حال سوختني
- I sold it to a pimp. Lester! - A pimp?
من اونو به اون جاكش ، لستر فروختم  - جاكش؟  -
Shit! What you waiting on for?
خوب ، منتظر ي هستي؟
Where can I find him?
كجا مي تونم يداش كنم؟
- I need to fucking know now! - He booked a cab! Union Fleet. Ask them!
من الان بايد بدونم  - اون تو يونيون فليت تاكسي راني داره ، از اونا برس -
Stay here. Do not move.
همون جا بمون ، تكون نخور
I’m not touching it. Get away from me. Fuck you!
من بهش دست نزدم از من دور شو
wow, you little shit! Just bit me!
لعنتي ، به من ضربه زدي
Who the hell is that? I’ll go see. Throw me my robe.
اين ديه كيه؟ - مي رم ببينم ، لباسم رو بده  -
Take the kids into the bedroom.
اون به رو ببر تو اتاق خواب
- May I help you? - I’m looking for Oleg.
مي  تونم كمكتون كنم؟  - اومدم دنبال اول  -
- Oleg. You must have the wrong address. -No. He's a ten -year-old boy.
اول ، احتمالا آدرس رو اشتباه اومديد - نه ، اون يه سر 10 ساله ست  -
He's pale. He never smiles.
خيلي رن و رو رفته ست ، اصلا هم نمي خنده
He's my neighbor’s kid. He called me from this apartment.
اون به همسايه مونه اون از اين آارتمان به من زن زد
Owens Park Lane, apartment 303.
ارك اوون ، شماره 303
Well, he must have given you the wrong address.
اون به شما آدرس اشتباهي داده
Or maybe you heard wrong. There's no Oleg.
يا شايدم شما اشتباه شنيديد اينجا اولي وجود نداره
He said that he was being held against his will.
اون به من فت كه اونو بر خلاف ميلش نه داشتند
That's ridiculous. There's only my husband and my two children inside.
اين خيلي مسخره است الان همسرم و دوتا به هام اون تو هستند
- No-one else. And it's late. - Well...
كس ديه اي نيست ، و الانم دير وقته  - خوب  -
I would like to take a look inside to satisfy my curiosity.
من مي خوان بيام تو و يه ناهي بندازم فقط از رو كنجكاوي
This is absurd. Are you suggesting I kidnapped Oleg?
مسخره ست شما فكر مي كنيد من اول رو دزدم؟
You know what? I’m gonna call the police. I’m gonna stand here waiting for them to arrive.
مي دوني يه؟ من الان زن مي زنم به ليس و منتظر مي شم تا اونا بيان
When all’s you gotta do is just let me in.
اون موقع شما به من اجازه ميديد كه بيام تو
If you must.
اه مي خواي
- Do you mind? - Go right ahead.
مشكلي نيست؟  - ادامه بديد -
The children 's room is on the right.
اتاق به ها سمت راسته
They are asleep.
اونا خوابيدن
Please go right in.
بريد تو
- Hello. - Don't ask, it's too ridiculous.
سلام  - سولي نرس ، خيلي مسخره ست  -
Sorry, I’m really embarrassed.
معذرت مي خوام ، من واقعا يج شدم
Excuse me, but I seriously doubt he's hiding in there.
معذرت مي خوام ولي من شك دارم كه اون ، اون تو قايم شده باشه
- What's through here? - Playroom.
اينجا يه؟  - اتاق بازي  -
Whoa.
واي
You guys got your own little Disneyland in here.
شما ديزني لند ُ اينجا درست كردين
Well, it's all about the children. And as you can see, there's no Oleg.
اينا ماله به هاست و همون طور كه ديد اولي در كار نيست
I really hope that you find him.
من واقعا اميدوارم كه يداش كنيد
You hear too many stories these days.
اين روزا اتفاقاي زيادي براي شما افتاده
- God only knows if it were our children. - If it were your children...photographs.
خدا مي دونه كه اونا به هاي ما هستند  - اه اونا به هاي شما هستند ...  عكس  -
- Excuse me! - Photographs.
ببخشيد  - عكس  -
No photographs.
هي عكسي نيست
If they were your children, you would have...
... اه اونا به هاي شما هستند ، را ازشون
at least one photograph somewhere in this apartment.
تو اين خونه يه عكسم ندارين
This is ridiculous! We only moved into this place. Everything’s in storage.
ما تازه اومديدم تو اين خونه هنوز همه يز رو از بسته هاش در نياورديم
Now I really must ask you to leave! I insist!
من واقعا ازتون مي خوام كه از اين جا بريد
Oleg?
اول؟
Oh, man. This is too much.
... اوه ، اينجا خيلي
It’s too much.
عجيبه
- It’s like some kind of a lure. - You're making a mistake.
اينجا خيلي ول زننده ست  - شما اشتباه مي كنيد  -
Tell her to leave, Dez.
ازش بخواه كه بره ،دز
Ma'am, if you don't leave right now, I’m calling the police.
خانوم اه شما الان اينجا رو ترك نكنيد من زن مي زنم به ليس
Call them. Call them. And mention you've got two abducted children in the next room.
آره ، بهشون زن بزنيد وبيد كه تو اون اتاق دو تا به هستند كه دزديده شدند
Two children who don't appear in any photographs in this house.
دو تا به كه ازشون تو اين خونه يه دونه عكسم نيست
- Where is Oleg? - How dare you suggest that we...
اول كجاست؟  - جور جرات مي كني؟  -
Oh...
اوه
Where's the boy?
سره كجاست؟
Where is he?
اون كجاست؟
Oh, my God. Oh...
اوه ، خداي من
You better pray he's not dead.
بهتره دعا كنيد كه نمرده باشه
Back off, you sick fuck!
بررد ، كثافت جنده
Jesus. Oh, God, help me.
خداي من ، كمك كن
Come on, come on, come on.
يالا ، يالا ، يالا
I said back the fuck up!
بهت فتم بررد
You sick, twisted, motherfucking cunt!
كثافت كس كش مادر جنده
Oh...
اوه
- Oh, wake up.
اوه بلند شو
That's right. That's right. Breathe. You're gonna be OK.
خوبه ، خوبه نفس بكش  ، همه يز درست ميشه
You can breathe, Oleg. I’m right here.
نفس بكش اول ، من همين جام
I’m right here, just breathe.
من همين جام، نفس بكش
- That's right
خوبه
Back off!
بررد عقب
I said back off!
فتم بررد
I will blow you away!
مي كشمت
OK. Can you get up?
خيلي خوب ، مي توني بلند شي؟
OK. Go to the bedroom. Get the two kids. Bring them downstairs. Nicky's there.
خوب ، برو تو اتاق خواب ، اون دوتا به رو با خودت ببر ايين ، نيك اونجاست
All right? Wait with him. OK? Move over.
خوب ؟ يش اون بمون بريد كنار
Get out of his way.
از سر راه بريد كنار
I’ve got a safe in the bedroom There's 100.000 cash in there and diamonds
من تو اتاق خواب يه او صندوق دارم كه توش 100 هزار دلار ول به همراه الماس هست
All you gotta do is take the boy and walk away.
همه رو وردار و با اون سر برو
Oh, my God. Oh...
اوه ، خداي من
Oh...
اوه
Oh, you sick fucks.
اوه ، مريض ها ي كثافت
You're right. We're sick.
شما راست مي يد ، ما مريض هستيم
We are, We're sick This Is really great This Is gonna help us
ما مريض هستيم اينا به ما كمك مي كنه
- Give me your phone. - Please, yeah.
تلفنت رو بده من  - خواهش مي كنم ، بفرماييد  -
- What are you doing? - She wants...
ي كار دار ي مي كني؟  - ... اون مي خواد  -
Who are you calling?
به كي زن مي زني؟
911 What is the nature of your emergency?
911مورد اضطراري شما يه؟
I just heard shooting across the hall. 1456, Owens Park Lane.
من مي خوام يه تيز اندازي تو ارك اوون شماره1456 رو ذارش كنم
What Is your name ma'am?
اسم شما يه ، خانوم؟
You're not serious.
جدي كه نمي ي؟
OK.
خيلي خوب
Hey. Hey, listen, one of your cabs just picked up my brother at AI’s Automotive.
هي، هي ، يكي از راننده هاي شما ماشين دادش منو برداشته
Yeah, well, listen to me.
آره ، به من وش كن
I was supposed to pick him up, but there's been a family emergency.
من فكر كزدم اون اومده و اونو برده ولي مثل اينكه براش يه مشكل خانوادي يش اومده
So, what I need you to do is l need you to find out where the cab dropped him off at.
تنها يزي كه مي خوام بدونم اينه كه كي اون ماشين رو برداشته
Yeah, call me back. My phone number's 555-7556.
باشه ، بهم زن بزن شماره من 7556 555
Hello? Yeah.
الو؟ بله
Hey, wait, wait, wait. Hey, calm down.
هي ، آروم ، آروم ، صبر كن
- What happened to your face? - It’s nothing.
صورتت ي شده؟  - يزي نشده  -
- I need to talk to you, Joe. - Later.
بايد ياهات حرف بزنم  - بعداً  -
No, now!
نه ، همين الان
Why couldn't you have just taken the kid and left?
را اون به ها رو ول نكردي بري؟
I have never seen evil before tonight, Joe.
من تا امشب همين شياطيني نديده بودم،جو
Real fucking evil.
شيطان هاي واقعي
OK?
خوب؟
And I know that's not what I see when I look in your eyes.
و اينو مي دونم وقتي تو شمات ناه مي كنم اينو تو شمات نمي بينم
Thanks a lot, Tee.
خيلي ممنون ، تي
- I’m trying to make a point here. - I know what point you're trying to make!
من مي خوام اينجا يه قراري بذارم - مي دونم ه قراري مي خواي بذاري  -
I did not marry an evil man, OK?
من با يه مرد شيطان صفت ازدواج نكردم ، باشه؟
I did not marry an evil man.
من با يه مرد شيطان صفت ازدواج نكردم
Shady, sleazy, mixed up with the wrong kind of people.
آدم مرموز و شل و ول تركيبي از آدم هاي خلاف كار
But definitely not evil.
ولي نه شيطاني
I know what you're trying to say, Tee.
من مي دونم ي مي خواي بي ، تي
Do you?
تو شيطان صفتي؟
I hope so. I have turned my back on a lot of things since we've been married.
اميدوارم ، من از اول ازدواجمون خيلي يزها رو ناديده رفتم
My eyes are wide open on this one
ولي شمام در اين مورد بازه بازه
Nicky, go home with your mom.
نيكي ، با مامانت برو خونه
Oleg, let's go take a ride.
اول ، بيا با هم بريم
What kind of music you listen to?
جور آهني دوست داري؟
Huh?
هان؟
You listen to that techno shit?
تكنو دوست داري؟
You listen to rap music? You like rap music?
آهن ر وش مي دي؟
They don't have what I listen to on the radio.
اون آهني كه من دوست دارم راديو خش نمي كنه
Yeah, what's that?
آره ، اون يه؟
Kvasha. It’s my mother's tape from Russia.
كاواشا ، نوارشو مامانم از روسيه آورده
What the fuck?
ي؟
Kvassna?
كاواشا؟
You're American, not Russian. Why listen to that shit?
تو آمريكايي هستي را به اونا وش  مي دي؟
My mother said I started in her belly in Russia, so I’m Russian.
مادرم ميه من تو روسيه رفتم تو شكمش س من يه روسم
You're not a Russian, you're an American, cos you were born in the USA.
تو روسي نيستي، تو تو آمريكا بدنيا اومدي س يه آمريكايي هستي
You're an American. An American.
تو تو آمريكايي ، و يه آمريكايي هستي
Say, "I’m an American." You say it.
بو من يه آمريكايي هستم ، اينو بو
Say, "I’m an American."
بو من  يه آمريكايي هستم
- I’m an American. - American.
من يه آمريكايي هستم آمريكايي
You were born in the fucking USA. That makes you an American.
تو تو آمريكا بدنيا اومدي س يه آمريكايي هستي
Listen to this.
اينو وش كن
He'll warm up the back seat for you when you're ready to get laid.
اون اين آهن رو براي تو خونده
You mark my words
به حرفام توجه كن
Fucking Kvasha.
كاواشاي لعنتي
Christ! You put me through the ringer tonight. You know that, don't you?
تو امشب منو تو دردسر انداختي اينو مي دونستي؟
- Hmm? - I won't say nothing.
هوم؟  - من يزي نفتم  -
Yeah, what'd you say to the cops?
تو به ليس ها ي فتي؟
- What'd you say to the cops? - I got the gun from Stevie Monroe's locker.
تو به ليس ها ي فتي؟  - فتم اونو از استيوي مونرو رفتم  -
He doesn't go there no more.
اون ديه اونجا نبود
Nicky told me to say that.
نيكي بهم فت اينوبم
Nicky told you to say that?
نيكي بهت فت اينو بي؟
Smart kid.
به ي باهوش
He's my best friend. We're gonna play for the Razors.
اون بهترين دوست منه ما براي ريزورز بازي مي كنيم
- Yeah?
بله؟
Hello?
الو؟
Yeah, that was me.
آره ، من بودم
The Royal Towers? How long ago?
رويال تاور؟ ه مدت قبل؟
All right, thanks.
باشه ، مرسي
Hold on. We're gonna go reclaim some stolen property.
ما ميريم يه يز دزديده شده رو س بيريم
Don't worry about it. We're just gonna sit tight for a while.
نرانش نباش فقط يه كم حواسمون رو بايد جمع كنيم
You know...
مي دوني
..I used to know this kid.
من بايد اين به رو بشناسم
His old man was a real fucking piece of shit.
درش واقعا آدم بيخوديه
Always drunk.
هميشه مسته
Always smacking him and his mom around.
هميشه اونو  و مادرش رو كتك مي زنه
This kid, he takes his licks... and waits this old fucking prick out.
اون به آماده ميشه
On the morning of his 14th birthday,
در صبح تولد 14 ساليش
he walks into his old man 's room with a baseball bat.
اون با يه وب بيسبال ميره تو اتاق اون مرد
Then he Mark McGwire's the fucking living shit out of him.
بعد اون مارك مك واير هستش كه در اونو در بياره
After that, the old man, he can't even hold a spoon without shaking.
بعد از اين اون مرد  ديه نمي تونه يه قاشق رو بدون لرزش دستش بيره
He don't remember things too good either.
و ديه اون يزها رو به خوبي يادش نمياد
He's neutralized.
اون خنثي ميشه
Which is a good thing.
كه يه اتفاق خوبه
Four more years max.
براي سال هاي سال
It’s more money.
ول بيشتر مي خوام
It’s lonely at the top
اون تنهايي تو  اوجه
Get your hands off Lester's property. That's my property.
به وسايل من دست نزن ، اون مال منه
I’m sorry
متاسفم
You stay right there don't you move
همين جا بمون ، تكون نخور
Stay just like that.
همين جوري بشين
What the fuck?
لعنتي
Jesus Christ, not now.
خداي من ، الان نه
Let's get in the cab.
بياين بريم تو ماشين
- I can hide it for you. -No, give it to me!
مي تونم اينو برات قايم كنم  - نه ، بدش به من -
They're gonna think you got the .38 and frisk you.
اونا فكر مي كنن كه اون تفن يش تو و تو رو ميردند
Come on. Give me the fucking gun.
يالا ، اون تفنُ بده من
Yo, Joe. What you got there?
هي ، جو، از كجا يداش كردي؟
He's a Christmas elf. I found him hitching a ride on Broad Street.
اون يه هديه كريسمسه اونو تو خيابون براود يدا كردم
Joey's a funny fucking guy, huh?
جويي آدم با مزه ايه ، نه؟
Let me take a guess, Joey.
بذار يه حدسي بزنم جويي
You were just about to call us.
تو مي خواستي به ما زن بزني
That's pretty good. You must have telepathy.
خيلي خوبه ،ما با هم تله اتي هم داريم
I must.
حتما
Give me your piece.
تفن بده من
Think I’m fucking around?
فكر مي كني من بيكارم؟
How about that, huh?
نظرت راجع به اون يه؟
Cocked and ready to go.
مسلح و آماده شليك
What are you, fucking nervous, tough guy?
را اينقدر عصبي هستي؟
You're gonna follow us, Joey.
تو بايد دنبال ما بيايي ، جويي
The kid will ride with us
به با ما مياد
Stay the fuck in the car.
تو ماشين بمون
Yeah? Nah, nah, I’m with him right now.
الو؟ نه نه ، من الان يششم
Are you 100 per cent?
مطمئني؟
You're a fucking idiot.
تو يه آدم احمقي
Nah, don't worry about it. I’m gonna take care of this motherfucker now.
نه ، نرانش نباش من مراقب ايت مادر جنده هستم
Come on, what the fuck?
ه خبره؟
You're gonna fucking whack me?
مي خواين منو كتك بزنيد؟
Come on, man! I told you. You got any doubts, I’ll tell you.
يالا ، اه به يزي شك داريد بيد من توضيح بدم
Shut your mouth. Shut your fucking mouth...now.
دهنت رو ببند اون دهن كيريت رو ببند
You see, my old man.
تو رييس منو ديدي
He says to me, "Nobody...
اون فت "هي كسي
knows nobody"
"هي كسي رو نمي شناسه
Would you fucking put that piece of shit away?
تو اون تفن رو م و ور كردي؟
- I fucking told you on my fucking family's... - Fucking family?
... من بهت فتم كه خانواده ام  - خانواده ات؟  -
When I leave here, I’m gonna fuck Teresa in the ass.
وقتي من از اينجا برم ميرم ترسا رو از كون مي كنم
That's how much I give a fuck about your family.
اين تنها اهميتي كه من به خانواده ات مي دم
On my fucking family, it ain't the fucking piece!
خانواده من به اون تفن هي ربطي نداره
How fucking far do we go back? How fucking long have we known each other?
ما قدر از هم دور شديم؟ ما ه مدته كه همدير رو مي شناسيم؟
Come on, what the fuck?
يالا ، ه مدته؟
- This is bullshit! - Like I said...
كثافت ها  - :  فكر كنم فتم  -
"Nobody knows nobody."
"هي كسي هي كسي رو نمي شناسه"
- Not in front of the fucking kid. - What kid?
جلوي اون به نه  - كدوم به؟ -
Listen, you knock this fucking gun out of my hand one more time,
وش كن ،اه يه بار ديه تفن رو از تو دستم بزني
I’m gonna blow your fucking brains all over this fucking place.
مغزت رو تو تمام اينجا خش مي كنم
And I’ll fuck that kid up right in front of you! You got that, nigger?
و اون به رو جلوي شمات مي كنم فهميدي كثافت؟
Nobody knows nobody! You got that?
هي كسي هي كسي رو نمي شناسه ، فهميدي؟
Shit! What the fuck?
لعنتي ،ي شد؟
Oh, shit.
لعنتي
You see, Pop...
ديدي ا
reached out to a friend of ours in the department.
يكي ديه از دوستامون رو از دست داديم
Turns out our friend Sal here was running his own little thing on the side.
رفيق مون "سال" همين جا مُرد
Hey, Sal!
هي ، سال
How's fucking business?
ت شده؟
Huh?
ها؟
They let him walk as a situated informant.
اونا ذاشتن اون از همه يز مطلع بشه
We just got confirmation ten minutes ago.
ما فقط10 دقيقه قبل اونو تاييد كرديم
Hey, hey! Hey, hey! Get the fuck up.
هي هي هي ، بلند شو
- Get the fuck up.
بلند شو
Yeah.
آره
Yeah?
بله؟
Oh, he's alone?
اون تنهاست؟
Go ahead. Give me the fucking number.
ادامه بده ، شمارش رو بده من
Have a Mai Tai on me, guys.
به من فن "ماي تاي" زديد رفقا
One Nike gym bag, 60 bucks.
يه كيف نايكي ، 60 دلار
You motherfucking guinea, cocksucking...
مادر جنده هاي عوضي
One Nokia cell phone...100 bucks.
يه وشي نوكيا ، 100 دلار
You have just fucked yourselves!
شما فقط خودتون رو اييديد
One ounce of Semtex...
semtexيه اونس
- 500 bucks
500دلار
Getting rid of a dirty cop...
از شر يه ليس خلاص شديم
..fucking priceless.
قدر ارزون
Now...the jury's still out on you, pal. So do me a favor.
ولي هنوز  هيات منصفه دنبال تو كاري كه من   مي خوام رو انجام بده
Get your ass in that car and follow me. And hey! Hey!
كونت رو بذار تو ماشين و دنبال من بيا
Don't get lost.
فرار نكن
I’m not fucking gonna.
فرار نمي كنم
Come on down. Come on down.
بيا ايين ، بيا ايين
How you doing?
حالت طوره؟
So...
... خوب
You wanna see something really cool?
مي خواي يه يز باحال بهت نشون بدم؟
Mm?
هوم؟
It’s called Jet Ice.
Jet lce  به اين مين
Black light paint.
ماورا بنفشه
You gotta do crazy shit like this to fill the seats
تو تو اين نور ديوانه مي شي
Now, Oleg
حالا ، اول
this is very serious matter
اين موضوع خيلي جديه
This man.
اين مرد
He give you the gun to shoot Anzor?
اون تفن رو بهت داده تا به آنزور شليك كني؟
Bullshit
لعنتي
He gave it to you! He told you to whack me!
اون اينو بهت داده و بهت فته به من شليك كني
- Stop fucking protecting him! - You shut the fuck up.
از اون طرفداري نكن  - خفه خون بير-
Oleg You listen to me
اول ، به من وش كن
Where did you get gun?
اون تفن رو از كجا  آوردي؟
At school. I found it in a locker.
تو مدرسه ، اون ازيه كمد يدا كردم
Don't you fucking touch him! Don't touch him!
به اون دست نزن ، دست نزن
- Touch him and I’ll fucking kill you! - You shut the fuck up!
به اون دست بزني مي كشمت  - خفه خون بير  -
- Your turn is coming - Yeah? Well, fucking eat me!
وقتت تموم شد  - آره ، س بيا منو بخور  -
You fucking Vor cocksucking bitch, fuck you!
كس كش ، كس ننه ، مي كنمت
- What did you call me? - You heard me. Fuck you, you fucking bitch.
ي فتي؟  - همون كه شنفتي، مي كنمت ، مي امت  -
I’m impressed. You know Vors.
تحت تاثير قرار رفتم
Vor V Zakonye, the Brotherhood.
راجع به برادريهVor v zakonye,
If you were smart man,
اه آدم باهوشي باشي
you would learn to fear this symbol.
از اين نشونه خواهي ترسيد
Fuck you and fuck your brotherhood Vors.
خودت و اوت برادريت رو اييدم
Cos I don't fucking answer to you. Fuck you!
ون من به تو هي جوابي نمي دم
Gonna let him muscle me around?
را مي ذاري با من اينجوري رفتار كنه؟
We're just trying to establish some truth here, Joe.
ما فقط مي خواييم اعتمادمون رو بيشتر كنيم
To be honest, I think the man's got some grounds for inquiry.
بيا صادق باشيم اون فقط مي خواد ازت ندتا سوال برسه
That's fucking bullshit! I told you, I didn't give the kid the fucking piece!
من بهتون فتم من اون تفن رو به اون به ندادم
Come on, Frankie!
يالا ، فرانكي
Come on, what the fuck, Frankie? I told you! I didn't give him the fucking piece.
يالا فرانكي ، بهت فتم من اون تفن رو بهش ندادم بهت فتم من اون تفن رو بهش ندادم
Don't let him hurt the kid, Anzor. Don't you fucking hurt the kid!
نذار به اون به صدمه بزنن ، آنزور با اون به كاري نداشته باشيد
You fuck! You fucking motherfuckers!
مادر جنده ها
I’m gonna fucking kill you! Oh, shit!
مي كشمت
Fuck you, Tommy!
اييدمت ، تامي
Don't you do this, Frankie.
تو اين كارو نمي كني ، فرانكي
Don't you do it!
تو اين كارو نمي كني
- Don't you fucking let him do this!
تو نمي ذاري اونا اين كارو بكنن
I’m not fucking lying!
من دروغ نمي م
Fuck!
لعنتي
Jesus tell them what they wanna know!
هر ي اونا مي خوان بهشون بو
Fuck, I told you I didn't know anything, Frankie!
بهت فتم من يزي نمي دونم ، فرانكي
Fuck!
لعنت
A fucking human hockey puck.
ه بازي قشني
I’m gonna fucking kill you!
مي كشمت
Oh you 're gonna kill me? You 're gonna fucking kill me?
تو منو مي كشي؟
- Give Anzor the gun. Kill the kid. - Frankie don't let him do this!
تفن رو بده آنزور ، اون به رو بكش  - فرانكي نذار اين كارو بكنه  -
I’m gonna fucking kill you!
مي كشمت
Don't let them do this
نذار اين كارو بكنن
What do you want me to do? You brought it on yourself
از من ي مي خواي؟ خودتون اونو آوردين
No, don't!
نه ، اين كارو نكن
Don't do it! Don't!
اين كارو نكن
I’ll fucking talk!
حرف مي زنم
I’ll fucking tell you whatever you wanna fucking hear!
بهتون مي م هر ي بخوايين بهتون مي م
No, my friend! First you will see that I am serious.
نه ، دوست من اول مي بيني كه من شوخي ندارم
Then afterwards, believe me, you will talk!
بعد از اون بهت قول مي دم كه به حرفات وش بدم
Oh, come on! Jesus Christ, I fucking told you!
اوه ، خداي من ، بهتون مي م
I fucking told you, I’ll tell you whatever you wanna hear, you fucking motherfucker.
همه يز رو بهتون مي م مادر جنده ها
Finish it! Do it right this time.
تمومش كنيد ، همين الان
No, Anzor! Anzor, look at me! Don't fucking do it!
نه آنزور ، اين كار رو نكن
Shut up!
خفه شو
I said finish it.
فتم تمومش كن
He's not your blood!
خونش به اي تو نيست
Don't fucking do it!
اين كار رو نكن
If you do it, I swear to God you better swallow a bullet!
اه اين كارو بكنب درتو در  ميارم
There's no way you'd be able to live with yourself!
ديه راهي نداره كه بتوني زنده بموني
Trust me, Anzor! Don't do it!
به من اعتماد كن اين كار رو نكن
Say something bad about the Duke.
دوباره راجع به دوك بد حرف بزن
Let me hear you call him a faggot.
يه بار ديه بهش بو بدردنخور
Come on!
يالا
- Say it. - No.
بو - نه  -
Shoot him!
بهش شليك كن
What are you fucking doing?
ي كار  داري  مي كني؟
Pick up the fucking gun
اون تفن رو بردار
Pick it up
برش دار
You do it
تو اين كارو مي كني
Gutless piece of faggot shit!
بدردنخور
Come on faggot!
يالا بدردنخور
I said finish it!
فتم تمومش كن
Pick it up and use it!
برش دار و شليك كن
Don't you fucking walk away from me!
از من دور نشو
Get up...
بلند شو
you fuck.
اييدمت
Fucking bullshit.
كثافت عوضي
Fuck. Fuck!
لعنتي
Fuck you, Frankie! I ain't taking the fucking heat for you no more.
اييدمت فرانكي من ديه براي تو كار نمي كنم
It wasn’t supposed to go down this way!
تو داري با طناب اره اون مي ري تو اه
- What are you talking about? - Czar of Brighton...
داري راجع به ي حرف مي زني؟  - تزار برايتون  -
Vor, whatever the fuck you are!
يا هري اسمش رو مي خواي بذارvor
Fucking didn't like it, did you, your nephew was...
از اين خوشت نمي ياد ، نه ، برادر زاده ات
was cooking and dealing in the neighborhood.
داشت تو خونه بقلي غذا درست مي كرد
That's what he said.
اون فت
He said, "Oleg, send him a message!"
"اون فت "اول يه يغامي بهش بده
Said "Let's use the kid"
اون فت از به سو استفاده كن
Would I put our thing in jeopardy for some two-bit fucking meth lab?
فكر كردي من تمام داراييام رو بخاطر يه غذا ختن به خطر مي ندازم؟
Think about it, OK? That's number one.
خوب روش فكر كن ، باشه؟ اين شماره يك
Number two.
شماره دو
I don't even live in that fucking neighborhood! What do I care if it blows up?
من همسايه اون نبودم س به كشتن اون اهميتي نمي دم
The gun.
اون تفنه
it was Tommy's! You fuck!
اون مال تاميه ، لعنتي
Tommy! Tommy, don't get involved in a goddamn jock fight. It’s all bullshit!
تامي ، تامي ، خودت رو قاطي نكن اين يه جن مسخره ست
He fucking put it in my right hand.
اون خودش تفن رو ذاشت تو دست راستم
A fucking snub nose .38, stainless steel. it was Tommy's gun!
اون تفن فولادي ضد زن شماره 38 لعنتي اون تفت مال تاميه
You motherfucker. I told you to get rid of that fucking piece.
مادر جنده من بهت فتم از شر اون خلاص شو
Yeah, well, not to my fucking recollection!
من يزي يادم نمياد
He said, "interest the tweaker's kid in the piece."
"اون فت "اون تفن رو بده به اون به
Ask the kid!
از به بخواه
Mr. Gazelle, he gave me the gun.
آقاي َزل تفن رو داد به من
He said I’d get to go to the game if... if I shot Anzor.
اون به من فت اه به آنزور شليك كنم براي من بليط بازي رو مي خره
it would make his friends happy.
اون فت اين كار دوستش رو خوشحال مي كنه
I’m sorry, kid.
متاسفم به
OK. OK. Fuck this bullshit.
باشه ،باشه ،مي كنمت
Fuck you, Joey, you fucking bastard!
مي كنمت
You're fucking dead, nigger!
تو يه آدم مرده اي
- Oh, I’m fucking shot! - That's some bad motherfucker!
من تير خوردم  - مادر به خطا ها   -
Fucking Vor!
لعنتي Vor!
Fuck you, cocksucker!
مي كنمت ، كس كش
You son of a bitch!
حروم زاده
- You're dying, motherfucker!
مي كشمت ، مادر جنده
Where's the fucking gun?
اون تفن لعنتي كجاست؟
Mr. Gazelle!
آقاي زل
Fuck you.
لعنت به تو
Oh...
اوه
Get off him, you fuck!
برو كنار
Do you know you got my son killed, you fucking scumbag?
مي دوني به من رو به كشتن دادي؟ كثافت
Oh, Frankie.
اوه ، فرانكي
I’m glad it's you cos there's something I’ve been...
... من خوشحالم كه تو باعث شدي
I’ve really been meaning to get off my chest.
كه بتونم از اين مخمصه بيام بيرون
You rat cocksucker! All of this fucking time!
كثافت ، اين همه مدت
Yeah, this whole fucking time!
آره ، اين همه مدت
This whole fucking time!
اين همه مدت
But we don't have your finger on the trigger, so do me! It’s one more nail in your coffin!
ولي ما به حرف تو وش نمي داديم
Oh, you got all that, do you?
تو باعث اين ماجرا شدي؟
How come it took you so long, then, huh, tough guy? Huh?
س را اينقدر طول كشيد؟ هان؟
How come? So fucking long! Tell me!
هان ، را اينقدر طول كشيد؟
You had to climb into bed with Yugorsky, didn't you?
توبا يوورسكي همدست بودي
I was all but out and you had to go and mix it up with the fucking Russians.
من از همه يز مطلع بودم ولي تو موضوع رو با اون روسي قاطي كردي
12 years undercover and my own wife don't even fucking know.
12سال و حتي زنمم خبر نداشت
Oh, you cocksucker. You don't have to worry.
كثافت ، نمي خواد نران باشي
She ain't never gonna hear it from your fucking lips anyhow!
اون ديه اينو از زبون خودت نمي شنوه
You fucking scumbag!
كثافت
I’ll tell her all about it while she sucks my fucking dick!
من همه يز بهش مي م وقتي اون تمام كير منو ساك زد
Come on. Come on!
يالا ، يالا
Are you fucking kidding me?
داري با من شوخي مي كني؟
What are you gonna do with that little boy?
مي خواي با اون تفن ي كار كني؟
You know that I had a little boy? My Tommy.
مي دونستي من يه سر  كوولو داشتم ، تامي كوولو
At one time he was your age
يه وقت كه اون هم سن تو بود
What are you gonna do with that, kid? What are you gonna do?
با اون مي خواي ي كار كني ، به؟ مي خواي ي كار كني؟
What are you gonna do with that, you Cheerio-bred, little motherfucker!
مادر جنده ي عوضي
Let's go home.
بيا بريم خونه
in position!
در موقعيت هستم
All right. On the other side. Let's go!
باشه ،اون طرف ي؟
Jesus Christ, Joey, we got shorted out.
خداي من ، ما تو رو م كرديم
We lost you back in Newark.
ما صدات رو نداشتيم
You were headed for Little Odessa.
داشتي راجع به اودسا حرف مي زدي
I’m taking the kid home to his mom.
من به رو مي برم خونه
Joey, where are you going?
جويي ، كجا داري مي ري؟
You're hurt. We gotta get you to a hospital.
تو آسيب ديدي، بايد ببريمت  بيمارستان
I’m going home.
من مي رم خونه
What are you thinking?
به ي فكر مي كني؟
I don't wanna go home.
من نمي خوام برم خونه
Well, I’m next door to you, remember, and I’m gonna be keeping my eye on you.
خوب ، ما با هم همسايه ايم ، يادت مي آد؟ من مراقبت هستم
Why don't we get breakfast before we have to start making with the heavy explaining?
را ما قبل از اينكه بريم خونه وشروع به توضيح دادن كنيم يه صبحانه رديف نخوريم؟
Get ourselves cleaned up a bit.
و خودمون رو يك كم تر تميز كنيم
Hey, listen.
وش كن
I’m taking Nick to the game on Friday night.
من مي خوام نيك رو جمعه شب ببرم بازي رو ببينه
Maybe we could find another ticket.
شايد بتونيم يه بليط ديه هم يدا كنيم
If you would like to go, that is.
البته اه بخواي بيايي
All right, that's good.
باشه، خوبه
You want some more orange juice?
بازم آب رتقال مي خواي؟
All right.
باشه
Well, err...
خوب
What do you say, we get out of here?
وقتي از اينجا رفتيم ي مي خواي بي؟
Well, lookie, lookie.
سلام كوولو
If it ain't little Charlie Bronson.
... اه ارلي برانسوني نيست
One thing about Lester. He always makes good on a promise.
لستر كه هست اون هميشه به قولش عمل مي كنه
Hey, asshole!
كثافت
What the fuck are you doing?
داري ي كار مي كني؟
Say hello to my little friend.
به دوست كوولوي من سلام كنيد
That's real fucking original. What are you? A fucking cartoon?
اون تفن خودشه از كجا آورديش؟
I’m a Mac Daddy pimp. You know that.
من مك ددي جاكشم ، منو مي شناسي؟
And now I’m gonna cap your ass
حالا كونت رو جر مي دم
When I’m finished with you I’m gonna take your little punk friend
وقتي كارم با تو تموم شد مي رم سراغ اون رفيق كوولوت
and I’m gonna put him in my posse.
اونو با تمام قدرتم مي يرم
And I’m gonna pimp him out for a couple of months!
و واسه  ند ماه ازش سو استفاده ميكنم
And then I’m gonna take your knife and cut him from ear to ear!
بعد اقوت رو مي يرم و وش تا وش صورتت رو مي بُرم
Just like I should have done yesterday, you fuck!
درست كاري كه ديشب بايد مي كردم ، لعنتيا
I’m sure that sounds great to you in your pimp world.
مي دونم كه دنياي جا كشيت اين داد و هوار ها خيلي قشنه
But, listen. That's not the fucking thing you wanna do!
ولي وش كن تو اين كارو نمي كني
You wanna put down that fucking gun and walk away.
تو تفنت رو مي ذاري زمين و از اينجا ميري
Cos I swear to fucking God, I’ll fucking kill you! Stupid fucking pimp bitch!
ونكه به خدا قسم ، مي كشمت جنده  جاكش
Wrong!
اشتباه مي كني
Only one of us is walking out of here. Guess who.
فقط يه نفرمون از اينجا ميره بيرون حدس بزن اون كيه؟
Oleg, get behind me.
اول ، بيا شت من
Come on!
يالا
Oleg talk to me Come on! Talk to me!
اول با من حرف بزن، يالا با مت حرف بزن
You 're gonna make it
تو مي توني
Joey please You're bleeding
جويي ، لطفاً ،تو زخمي شدي
Fuck, fuck!
لعنتي
OLEG: Look out! Look out!
مواظب باش
Mr. Gazelle! Stop the car. We need to get some help.
آقاي زل ، ماشين رو نه دار بايد يه كمك يدا كنيم
Tee...
تي
- Please Mr. Gazelle! - Tee...I’m coming home.
آقاي زل ، خواهش مي كنم  - تي ، من دارم ميام خونه -
Mr. Gazelle, please! Stop the car. We need to get some help.
آقاي زل ، ماشين رو نه دار بايد يه كمك يدا كنيم
- I’ve gotta tell her. - You're hurt!
من همه يزو بهش مي م  - شما زخمي شديد -
You're bleeding!
شما زخمي شديد
God.
خداي من
- Joey!
جويي
Joey, please! Stop!
جويي ، وايسا
Mr. Gazelle, wake up!
آقاي زل ،بيدار شو
Mr. Gazelle! Wake up! Come on!
آقاي زل ،بيدار شو ،يالا
Stop the car! Stop the car!
ماشين رو نه دار ، ماشين رو نه دار
Please! Stop!
خواهش مي كنم وايسا
Joe?
جو؟
Mr. Gazelle, watch out!
آقاي زل ، مراقب باش
Joe! Joe!
جو، جو
Oleg, wait! Wait!
اول ،صبر كن ، صبر كن
Oh, God!
اوه ، خداي من
Mom! Mom!
مامان ، مامان
Joe!
جو
Jesus!
خداي من
Oh, fuck! Fuck!
لعنتي
Nicky! Call 911!
نيكي ، زن بزن 911
Don't do this to me, Joe.
نه، جويي اين كارو بامن نكن
- Don't fucking do this to me. - Oh, sweetheart.
اين كارو بامن نكن عزيزم -
I loved you.
من دوست دارم
OK?
باشه؟
Just remember.
يادت باشه
I was always the real Joey.
من هميشه جويي بودم
OK? I wasn't a liar.
باشه ؟ من دروغو نبودم
Shut up. Shut up. Look at me.
خفه شو، آروم باش
Look at me. Baby, look at me in the eye.
به من ناه كن عزيزم تو شمام ناه كن
Joey, look at me in the eyes. I don't care, OK? it doesn't matter.
جويي ،تو شمام ناه كن اصلا اهميتي نداره
I’m gonna kick your ass over it later.
من بعدا درت رو در ميارم
Stay with me, Joey! Stay! Look at me!
با من بمون ، جويي  به من ناه كن
Look at me, I’m right here! I’m right here for you!
به من ناه كن ، من همين جام من كنارتم
Nicky! Nicky, come here!
نيكي ، نيكي ، بيا اينجا
Nicky! Nicky!
نيكي ، نيكي
- He's right here. - They're coming.
اون اينجاست  - اونا دارن ميان  -
- They're on their way - OK.
اونا تو راهن - باشه  -
We're still going to the game Friday, Dad?
ما هنوز ميخوايم بريم بازي رو ببينيم، در؟
- I love you, Nick! - It’s OK.
دوست دارم نيك  - باشه  -
- He wants to go to the game, baby. - Yeah.
اون مي خواد بره بازي رو ببينه - آره  -
We're gonna go to the game.
ما ميريم بازي رو ميبينيم
- And fucking kick their asses, right, Mom? - They are going down big fucking time!
و كونشون رو اره مي كنيم  ، مامان  - و اونا لعنتيع سقوط مي كنن -
You have a bad mouth.
تو خيلي بد دهني
- It’s not that bad. You'll be OK. - Joe?
اونقدرم بد نيست ، تو خوب ميشي - جويي؟  -
I’m right here.
من همين جام
- Stay right... - I’m right here. I’m right here.
همين جا بمون  - من همين جام،من همين جام  -
Joe?
جويي؟
Joe? Oh, God, no, no!
جويي؟ خداي من نه، نه
Oh, God, no!
خداي من نه
Oh, God, Joe!
خداي من ، جويي
Get the kid outside! I don't want him going in there!
اون به رو ببر بيرون من نمي خوام اونجا باشه
Hey, Luis.
هي ، لوئيس
Hey, George?
هي ، جورج؟
- The alternator is in the car. - All right.
ترانسفورماتور تو ماشينه  - باشه  -
Don't ever ask me to bury you again, Joe.
ديه از من نخواه تو مراسم تدفينت شركت كنم ، جو
- What did they put in that coffin really? - What?
اونا تو اون تابوت ي ذاشتند؟  - ي ؟  -
- What did they put in the coffin? - in the coffin?
تو تابوت؟  -
- Yeah. - Why? Did it seem heavy?
آره يه خيلي سنين بود؟
I don't know. I’m thinking, probably a couple of blue shirts.
نمي دونم فكر كنم ند تا از لباس هاي تيم رقيب رو ذاشتند
Must have been Lashon and McCall.
و شايدم لاشون و مك كال بودند
- Does that sound good? - And Caimen.
از اون آهن خوشت مياد؟ - Kaimen. -
- You want some of this too? - For sure, Marishka.
از اينا زياد مي خواي؟  - حتما ، ماريشكا  -
Marishka, you want some of this too?
ماريشكا ، از اونام مي خواي؟
I’ll take the both of you right now. How about that?
من الان جفتتون رو ميبرم نظرتون يه؟
Razors.
ريزور